{"qid": "easy-0001", "question_type": "6", "question": "What percentage of NeurIPS papers have exactly 4 authors? In the authors column of the database, each entry is a list, not a single string. Return a value between 0 and 1.", "answer": 0.21311018131101814}
{"qid": "easy-0002", "question_type": "4", "question": "What is the title of the patent filed between 2012 and 2016 that took the longest number of days between the filing date and the publication date?", "answer": ["EVALUATING KEYWORD PERFORMANCE"]}
{"qid": "easy-0003", "question_type": "3", "question": "How does the number of patent applications filed in 2011 compare proportionally to those filed in the 2013? Return a number between 0 and 1. Please note that each row represents a unique patent application, and not all patent applications are assigned a patent number.", "answer": 0.593273174733388}
{"qid": "easy-0004", "question_type": "3", "question": "How does the number of patent applications filed in 2016 compare proportionally to those filed in the 2007? Return a number between 0 and 1. Please note that each row represents a unique patent application, and not all patent applications are assigned a patent number.", "answer": 4.818214285714285}
{"qid": "easy-0005", "question_type": "4", "question": "What is the title of the patent filed between 2016 and 2017 that took the longest number of days between the filing date and the publication date?", "answer": ["System and method for sterilizing and/or deimmunizing an object"]}
{"qid": "easy-0006", "question_type": "3", "question": "How does the number of patent applications filed in 2009 compare proportionally to those filed in the 2017? Return a number between 0 and 1. Please note that each row represents a unique patent application, and not all patent applications are assigned a patent number.", "answer": 0.10124413992066354}
{"qid": "easy-0007", "question_type": "3", "question": "How does the number of patent applications filed in 2015 compare proportionally to those filed in the 2005? Return a number between 0 and 1. Please note that each row represents a unique patent application, and not all patent applications are assigned a patent number.", "answer": 1.9240773286467487}
{"qid": "easy-0008", "question_type": "6", "question": "What proportion of NeurIPS papers have fewer than 8 authors? In the authors column of the database, each entry is a list, not a single string. Return a value between 0 and 1.", "answer": 0.8716875871687587}
{"qid": "easy-0009", "question_type": "1", "question": "What was the typical time span between the submission and approval of patents from 2007 to 2008? Return an integer representing the number of days by truncating the decimal part.", "answer": 1336}
{"qid": "easy-0010", "question_type": "2", "question": "What were the top 2 IPCR categories with the highest number of accepted patents in 2005? Return them as a list of IPCR categories.", "answer": ["G06", "H04"]}
{"qid": "easy-0011", "question_type": "4", "question": "What is the title of the patent filed between 2009 and 2011 that had the longest publication delay in terms of number of days between the filing date and the publication date?", "answer": ["DYNAMIC TISSUE HOLDING DEVICE WITH LOW PROFILE SPRING"]}
{"qid": "easy-0012", "question_type": "2", "question": "Which CPC categories were among the top 2 with the highest number of accepted patents in 2017? Return the top categories with the highest approval rates as a list of CPC categories.", "answer": ["H01", "H04"]}
{"qid": "easy-0013", "question_type": "3", "question": "How does the number of patent applications filed in 2008 compare proportionally to those filed in the 2011? Return a number between 0 and 1. Please note that each row represents a unique patent application, and not all patent applications are assigned a patent number.", "answer": 0.24764933628318583}
{"qid": "easy-0014", "question_type": "3", "question": "How does the number of patent applications filed in 2008 compare proportionally to those filed in the 2015? Return a number between 0 and 1. Please note that each row represents a unique patent application, and not all patent applications are assigned a patent number.", "answer": 0.3271830471318962}
{"qid": "easy-0015", "question_type": "4", "question": "What is the title of the patent filed between 2004 and 2011 that had the longest publication delay in terms of number of days between the filing date and the publication date?", "answer": ["Preserving document construct fidelity in converting graphic-represented documents into text-readable documents"]}
{"qid": "easy-0016", "question_type": "6", "question": "What percentage of NeurIPS papers have fewer than 8 authors? In the authors column of the database, each entry is a list, not a single string. Return a value between 0 and 1.", "answer": 0.8716875871687587}
{"qid": "easy-0017", "question_type": "4", "question": "What is the title of the patent filed between 2017 and 2017 with the longest number of days elapsed between the filing date and the publication date?", "answer": ["NUCLEIC ACID COMPOUNDS FOR BINDING GROWTH DIFFERENTIATION FACTOR 11"]}
{"qid": "easy-0018", "question_type": "6", "question": "What percentage of NeurIPS papers have more than 10 authors? In the authors column of the database, each entry is a list, not a single string. Return a value between 0 and 1.", "answer": 0.03430962343096234}
{"qid": "easy-0019", "question_type": "2", "question": "Which CPC categories were among the top 2 with the highest number of accepted patents in 2017? Return the top categories with the highest approval rates as a list of CPC categories.", "answer": ["H01", "H04"]}
{"qid": "easy-0020", "question_type": "6", "question": "What percentage of NeurIPS papers have more than 8 authors? In the authors column of the database, each entry is a list, not a single string. Return a value between 0 and 1.", "answer": 0.07670850767085077}
{"qid": "easy-0021", "question_type": "2", "question": "Which IPCR categories were among the top 2 with the highest number of accepted patents in 2010? Return the top categories with the highest approval rates as a list of IPCR categories.", "answer": ["G06", "H04"]}
{"qid": "easy-0022", "question_type": "2", "question": "Which IPCR categories were among the top 2 with the highest number of accepted patents in 2010? Return the top categories with the highest approval rates as a list of IPCR categories.", "answer": ["G06", "H04"]}
{"qid": "easy-0023", "question_type": "3", "question": "How does the number of patent applications filed in 2007 compare proportionally to those filed in the 2014? Return a number between 0 and 1. Please note that each row represents a unique patent application, and not all patent applications are assigned a patent number.", "answer": 0.2735176321187848}
{"qid": "easy-0024", "question_type": "6", "question": "What percentage of NeurIPS papers have fewer than 5 authors? In the authors column of the database, each entry is a list, not a single string. Return a value between 0 and 1.", "answer": 0.5101813110181311}
{"qid": "easy-0025", "question_type": "3", "question": "How does the number of patent applications filed in 2012 compare proportionally to those filed in the 2018? Return a number between 0 and 1. Please note that each row represents a unique patent application, and not all patent applications are assigned a patent number.", "answer": 0.06962322653387203}
{"qid": "easy-0026", "question_type": "2", "question": "Which IPCR categories were among the top 2 with the highest number of accepted patents in 2018? Return the top categories with the highest approval rates as a list of IPCR categories.", "answer": ["H04", "A61"]}
{"qid": "easy-0027", "question_type": "1", "question": "What was the average time between the filing and issuance of patents from 2015 to 2016? Return an integer representing the number of days by truncating the decimal part.", "answer": 609}
{"qid": "easy-0028", "question_type": "3", "question": "How does the number of patent applications filed in 2018 compare proportionally to those filed in the 2006? Return a number between 0 and 1. Please note that each row represents a unique patent application, and not all patent applications are assigned a patent number.", "answer": 13.359414225941423}
{"qid": "easy-0029", "question_type": "1", "question": "What was the average time between the filing and issuance of patents from 2008 to 2012? Return an integer representing the number of days by truncating the decimal part.", "answer": 1087}
{"qid": "easy-0030", "question_type": "4", "question": "What is the title of the patent filed between 2016 and 2016 that had the longest publication delay in terms of number of days between the filing date and the publication date?", "answer": ["System and method for sterilizing and/or deimmunizing an object"]}
{"qid": "easy-0031", "question_type": "2", "question": "Which IPCR categories were among the top 2 with the highest number of accepted patents in 2009? Return the top categories with the highest approval rates as a list of IPCR categories.", "answer": ["G06", "H04"]}
{"qid": "easy-0032", "question_type": "4", "question": "What is the title of the patent filed between 2006 and 2010 that took the longest number of days between the filing date and the publication date?", "answer": ["FUEL CARTRIDGE AND FUEL CELL USING THE SAME"]}
{"qid": "easy-0033", "question_type": "3", "question": "How does the number of patent applications filed in 2008 compare proportionally to those filed in the 2015? Return a number between 0 and 1. Please note that each row represents a unique patent application, and not all patent applications are assigned a patent number.", "answer": 0.3271830471318962}
{"qid": "easy-0034", "question_type": "4", "question": "What is the title of the patent filed between 2005 and 2008 that took the longest number of days between the filing date and the publication date?", "answer": ["FUEL CARTRIDGE AND FUEL CELL USING THE SAME"]}
{"qid": "easy-0035", "question_type": "3", "question": "How does the number of patent applications filed in 2004 compare proportionally to those filed in the 2014? Return a number between 0 and 1. Please note that each row represents a unique patent application, and not all patent applications are assigned a patent number.", "answer": 1.1178079515483053}
{"qid": "easy-0036", "question_type": "5", "question": "Who were the top 2 authors with the most publications amongst the first 1400 papers at NeurIPS? In the authors column of the database, each entry is a list, not a single string. Return as a list of authors.", "answer": ["Bernhard Schölkopf", "Mihaela van der Schaar"]}
{"qid": "easy-0037", "question_type": "3", "question": "How does the number of patent applications filed in 2014 compare proportionally to those filed in the 2005? Return a number between 0 and 1. Please note that each row represents a unique patent application, and not all patent applications are assigned a patent number.", "answer": 3.5982425307557118}
{"qid": "easy-0038", "question_type": "6", "question": "What's the ratio of NeurIPS papers that have fewer than or equal to 5 authors? In the authors column of the database, each entry is a list, not a single string. Return a value between 0 and 1.", "answer": 0.6728033472803348}
{"qid": "easy-0039", "question_type": "4", "question": "What is the title of the patent filed between 2006 and 2012 that took the longest number of days between the filing date and the publication date?", "answer": ["FUEL CARTRIDGE AND FUEL CELL USING THE SAME"]}
{"qid": "easy-0040", "question_type": "5", "question": "Which 5 authors had the most publications where the titles contain 'Large Language Models' amongst the first 1900 papers at NeurIPS? In the authors column of the database, each entry is a list, not a single string. Return as a list of authors.", "answer": ["Sarath Sreedharan", "Karthik Valmeekam", "Yuan Cao", "Lintang Sutawika", "Subbarao Kambhampati"]}
{"qid": "easy-0041", "question_type": "3", "question": "How does the number of patent applications filed in 2012 compare proportionally to those filed in the 2013? Return a number between 0 and 1. Please note that each row represents a unique patent application, and not all patent applications are assigned a patent number.", "answer": 0.18236259228876128}
{"qid": "easy-0042", "question_type": "3", "question": "How does the number of patent applications filed in 2005 compare proportionally to those filed in the 2007? Return a number between 0 and 1. Please note that each row represents a unique patent application, and not all patent applications are assigned a patent number.", "answer": 1.0160714285714285}
{"qid": "easy-0043", "question_type": "3", "question": "How does the number of patent applications filed in 2017 compare proportionally to those filed in the 2015? Return a number between 0 and 1. Please note that each row represents a unique patent application, and not all patent applications are assigned a patent number.", "answer": 2.0263061746437705}
{"qid": "easy-0044", "question_type": "4", "question": "What is the title of the patent filed between 2007 and 2012 that took the longest number of days between the filing date and the publication date?", "answer": ["FUEL CARTRIDGE AND FUEL CELL USING THE SAME"]}
{"qid": "easy-0045", "question_type": "4", "question": "What is the title of the patent filed between 2005 and 2013 with the longest number of days elapsed between the filing date and the publication date?", "answer": ["FUEL CARTRIDGE AND FUEL CELL USING THE SAME"]}
{"qid": "easy-0046", "question_type": "6", "question": "What proportion of NeurIPS papers have fewer than 8 authors? In the authors column of the database, each entry is a list, not a single string. Return a value between 0 and 1.", "answer": 0.8716875871687587}
{"qid": "easy-0047", "question_type": "3", "question": "How does the number of patent applications filed in 2005 compare proportionally to those filed in the 2013? Return a number between 0 and 1. Please note that each row represents a unique patent application, and not all patent applications are assigned a patent number.", "answer": 0.23338802296964725}
{"qid": "easy-0048", "question_type": "4", "question": "What is the title of the patent filed between 2017 and 2017 that took the longest number of days between the filing date and the publication date?", "answer": ["NUCLEIC ACID COMPOUNDS FOR BINDING GROWTH DIFFERENTIATION FACTOR 11"]}
{"qid": "easy-0049", "question_type": "3", "question": "How does the number of patent applications filed in 2010 compare proportionally to those filed in the 2007? Return a number between 0 and 1. Please note that each row represents a unique patent application, and not all patent applications are assigned a patent number.", "answer": 0.3964285714285714}
{"qid": "easy-0050", "question_type": "3", "question": "How does the number of patent applications filed in 2010 compare proportionally to those filed in the 2011? Return a number between 0 and 1. Please note that each row represents a unique patent application, and not all patent applications are assigned a patent number.", "answer": 0.1534845132743363}
{"qid": "easy-0051", "question_type": "5", "question": "Who were the top 3 authors with the highest number of publications where the titles contain 'Large Language Models' amongst the first 2600 papers at NeurIPS? In the authors column of the database, each entry is a list, not a single string. Return as a list of authors.", "answer": ["Karthik Valmeekam", "Sarath Sreedharan", "Subbarao Kambhampati"]}
{"qid": "easy-0052", "question_type": "4", "question": "What is the title of the patent filed between 2007 and 2008 with the longest number of days elapsed between the filing date and the publication date?", "answer": ["FUEL CARTRIDGE AND FUEL CELL USING THE SAME"]}
{"qid": "easy-0053", "question_type": "1", "question": "What was the average time between the filing and issuance of patents from 2015 to 2018? Return an integer representing the number of days by truncating the decimal part.", "answer": 565}
{"qid": "easy-0054", "question_type": "6", "question": "What's the ratio of NeurIPS papers that have more than 9 authors? In the authors column of the database, each entry is a list, not a single string. Return a value between 0 and 1.", "answer": 0.0502092050209205}
{"qid": "easy-0055", "question_type": "3", "question": "How does the number of patent applications filed in 2005 compare proportionally to those filed in the 2014? Return a number between 0 and 1. Please note that each row represents a unique patent application, and not all patent applications are assigned a patent number.", "answer": 0.27791345120640815}
{"qid": "easy-0056", "question_type": "5", "question": "Who were the top 4 authors with the highest number of publications where the titles contain 'Large Language Models' amongst the first 3200 papers at NeurIPS? In the authors column of the database, each entry is a list, not a single string. Return as a list of authors.", "answer": ["Karthik Valmeekam", "William Yang Wang", "Sarath Sreedharan", "Subbarao Kambhampati"]}
{"qid": "easy-0057", "question_type": "2", "question": "Which IPCR categories were among the top 2 with the highest number of accepted patents in 2005? Return the top categories with the highest approval rates as a list of IPCR categories.", "answer": ["G06", "H04"]}
{"qid": "easy-0058", "question_type": "4", "question": "What is the title of the patent filed between 2007 and 2014 with the longest number of days elapsed between the filing date and the publication date?", "answer": ["FUEL CARTRIDGE AND FUEL CELL USING THE SAME"]}
{"qid": "easy-0059", "question_type": "1", "question": "What was the average time between the filing and issuance of patents from 2010 to 2013? Return an integer representing the number of days by truncating the decimal part.", "answer": 972}
{"qid": "easy-0060", "question_type": "3", "question": "How does the number of patent applications filed in 2015 compare proportionally to those filed in the 2013? Return a number between 0 and 1. Please note that each row represents a unique patent application, and not all patent applications are assigned a patent number.", "answer": 0.4490566037735849}
{"qid": "easy-0061", "question_type": "4", "question": "What is the title of the patent filed between 2005 and 2015 that took the longest number of days between the filing date and the publication date?", "answer": ["FUEL CARTRIDGE AND FUEL CELL USING THE SAME"]}
{"qid": "easy-0062", "question_type": "3", "question": "How does the number of patent applications filed in 2005 compare proportionally to those filed in the 2008? Return a number between 0 and 1. Please note that each row represents a unique patent application, and not all patent applications are assigned a patent number.", "answer": 1.588498045784478}
{"qid": "easy-0063", "question_type": "1", "question": "What was the typical time span between the submission and approval of patents from 2010 to 2014? Return an integer representing the number of days by truncating the decimal part.", "answer": 932}
{"qid": "easy-0064", "question_type": "2", "question": "What were the top 2 CPC categories with the highest number of accepted patents in 2014? Return them as a list of CPC categories.", "answer": ["H04", "G06"]}
{"qid": "easy-0065", "question_type": "1", "question": "What was the typical time span between the submission and approval of patents from 2013 to 2013? Return an integer representing the number of days by truncating the decimal part.", "answer": 912}
{"qid": "easy-0066", "question_type": "2", "question": "What were the top 2 IPCR categories with the highest number of accepted patents in 2013? Return them as a list of IPCR categories.", "answer": ["H04", "G06"]}
{"qid": "easy-0067", "question_type": "6", "question": "What proportion of NeurIPS papers have fewer than or equal to 8 authors? In the authors column of the database, each entry is a list, not a single string. Return a value between 0 and 1.", "answer": 0.9232914923291492}
{"qid": "easy-0068", "question_type": "1", "question": "What was the average duration between the filing and issuance of patents from 2006 to 2011? Return an integer representing the number of days by truncating the decimal part.", "answer": 1185}
{"qid": "easy-0069", "question_type": "6", "question": "What percentage of NeurIPS papers have fewer than 8 authors? In the authors column of the database, each entry is a list, not a single string. Return a value between 0 and 1.", "answer": 0.8716875871687587}
{"qid": "easy-0070", "question_type": "4", "question": "What is the title of the patent filed between 2010 and 2015 that took the longest number of days between the filing date and the publication date?", "answer": ["EVALUATING KEYWORD PERFORMANCE"]}
{"qid": "easy-0071", "question_type": "6", "question": "What percentage of NeurIPS papers have more than 7 authors? In the authors column of the database, each entry is a list, not a single string. Return a value between 0 and 1.", "answer": 0.12831241283124128}
{"qid": "easy-0072", "question_type": "6", "question": "What's the ratio of NeurIPS papers that have greater than or equal to 5 authors? In the authors column of the database, each entry is a list, not a single string. Return a value between 0 and 1.", "answer": 0.4898186889818689}
{"qid": "easy-0073", "question_type": "3", "question": "How does the number of patent applications filed in 2017 compare proportionally to those filed in the 2018? Return a number between 0 and 1. Please note that each row represents a unique patent application, and not all patent applications are assigned a patent number.", "answer": 0.34739578439663005}
{"qid": "easy-0074", "question_type": "4", "question": "What is the title of the patent filed between 2008 and 2008 with the longest number of days elapsed between the filing date and the publication date?", "answer": ["FUEL CARTRIDGE AND FUEL CELL USING THE SAME"]}
{"qid": "easy-0075", "question_type": "6", "question": "What percentage of NeurIPS papers have fewer than or equal to 6 authors? In the authors column of the database, each entry is a list, not a single string. Return a value between 0 and 1.", "answer": 0.7927475592747559}
{"qid": "easy-0076", "question_type": "3", "question": "How does the number of patent applications filed in 2010 compare proportionally to those filed in the 2004? Return a number between 0 and 1. Please note that each row represents a unique patent application, and not all patent applications are assigned a patent number.", "answer": 0.09700253430044568}
{"qid": "easy-0077", "question_type": "3", "question": "How does the number of patent applications filed in 2009 compare proportionally to those filed in the 2016? Return a number between 0 and 1. Please note that each row represents a unique patent application, and not all patent applications are assigned a patent number.", "answer": 0.08324067897116597}
{"qid": "easy-0078", "question_type": "5", "question": "Who were the top 5 authors with the most publications where the titles contain 'Large Language Models' amongst the first 1900 papers at NeurIPS? In the authors column of the database, each entry is a list, not a single string. Return as a list of authors.", "answer": ["Sarath Sreedharan", "Karthik Valmeekam", "Yuan Cao", "Lintang Sutawika", "Subbarao Kambhampati"]}
{"qid": "easy-0079", "question_type": "5", "question": "Who were the top 5 authors with the most publications where the titles contain 'Large Language Models' amongst the first 1800 papers at NeurIPS? In the authors column of the database, each entry is a list, not a single string. Return as a list of authors.", "answer": ["Karthik Valmeekam", "Lintang Sutawika", "Yuan Cao", "Sarath Sreedharan", "Subbarao Kambhampati"]}
{"qid": "easy-0080", "question_type": "2", "question": "Which IPCR categories were among the top 2 with the highest number of accepted patents in 2007? Return the top categories with the highest approval rates as a list of IPCR categories.", "answer": ["G06", "H04"]}
{"qid": "easy-0081", "question_type": "2", "question": "Which IPCR categories were among the top 2 with the highest number of accepted patents in 2014? Return the top categories with the highest approval rates as a list of IPCR categories.", "answer": ["H04", "G06"]}
{"qid": "easy-0082", "question_type": "4", "question": "What is the title of the patent filed between 2005 and 2010 with the longest number of days elapsed between the filing date and the publication date?", "answer": ["FUEL CARTRIDGE AND FUEL CELL USING THE SAME"]}
{"qid": "easy-0083", "question_type": "1", "question": "What was the average time between the filing and issuance of patents from 2016 to 2017? Return an integer representing the number of days by truncating the decimal part.", "answer": 499}
{"qid": "easy-0084", "question_type": "2", "question": "Which CPC categories were among the top 2 with the highest number of accepted patents in 2016? Return the top categories with the highest approval rates as a list of CPC categories.", "answer": ["H04", "H01"]}
{"qid": "easy-0085", "question_type": "2", "question": "Which IPCR categories were among the top 2 with the highest number of accepted patents in 2004? Return the top categories with the highest approval rates as a list of IPCR categories.", "answer": ["G06", "H04"]}
{"qid": "easy-0086", "question_type": "3", "question": "How does the number of patent applications filed in 2011 compare proportionally to those filed in the 2008? Return a number between 0 and 1. Please note that each row represents a unique patent application, and not all patent applications are assigned a patent number.", "answer": 4.037967615857063}
{"qid": "easy-0087", "question_type": "5", "question": "Who were the top 5 authors with the highest number of publications where the titles contain 'Large Language Models' amongst the first 2200 papers at NeurIPS? In the authors column of the database, each entry is a list, not a single string. Return as a list of authors.", "answer": ["Karthik Valmeekam", "Sarath Sreedharan", "Subbarao Kambhampati", "Yuan Cao", "Lintang Sutawika"]}
{"qid": "easy-0088", "question_type": "6", "question": "What's the ratio of NeurIPS papers that have more than 9 authors? In the authors column of the database, each entry is a list, not a single string. Return a value between 0 and 1.", "answer": 0.0502092050209205}
{"qid": "easy-0089", "question_type": "4", "question": "What is the title of the patent filed between 2008 and 2013 with the longest number of days elapsed between the filing date and the publication date?", "answer": ["FUEL CARTRIDGE AND FUEL CELL USING THE SAME"]}
{"qid": "easy-0090", "question_type": "1", "question": "What was the average time between the filing and issuance of patents from 2005 to 2009? Return an integer representing the number of days by truncating the decimal part.", "answer": 1318}
{"qid": "easy-0091", "question_type": "3", "question": "How does the number of patent applications filed in 2006 compare proportionally to those filed in the 2007? Return a number between 0 and 1. Please note that each row represents a unique patent application, and not all patent applications are assigned a patent number.", "answer": 0.8535714285714285}
{"qid": "easy-0092", "question_type": "3", "question": "How does the number of patent applications filed in 2008 compare proportionally to those filed in the 2011? Return a number between 0 and 1. Please note that each row represents a unique patent application, and not all patent applications are assigned a patent number.", "answer": 0.24764933628318583}
{"qid": "easy-0093", "question_type": "4", "question": "What is the title of the patent filed between 2012 and 2017 that took the longest number of days between the filing date and the publication date?", "answer": ["EVALUATING KEYWORD PERFORMANCE"]}
{"qid": "easy-0094", "question_type": "4", "question": "What is the title of the patent filed between 2004 and 2006 with the longest number of days elapsed between the filing date and the publication date?", "answer": ["Preserving document construct fidelity in converting graphic-represented documents into text-readable documents"]}
{"qid": "easy-0095", "question_type": "6", "question": "What proportion of NeurIPS papers have fewer than or equal to 5 authors? In the authors column of the database, each entry is a list, not a single string. Return a value between 0 and 1.", "answer": 0.6728033472803348}
{"qid": "easy-0096", "question_type": "4", "question": "What is the title of the patent filed between 2017 and 2017 with the longest number of days elapsed between the filing date and the publication date?", "answer": ["NUCLEIC ACID COMPOUNDS FOR BINDING GROWTH DIFFERENTIATION FACTOR 11"]}
{"qid": "easy-0097", "question_type": "2", "question": "Which IPCR categories were among the top 2 with the highest number of accepted patents in 2004? Return the top categories with the highest approval rates as a list of IPCR categories.", "answer": ["G06", "H04"]}
{"qid": "easy-0098", "question_type": "1", "question": "What was the average duration between the filing and issuance of patents from 2014 to 2016? Return an integer representing the number of days by truncating the decimal part.", "answer": 717}
{"qid": "easy-0099", "question_type": "6", "question": "What percentage of NeurIPS papers have greater than or equal to 8 authors? In the authors column of the database, each entry is a list, not a single string. Return a value between 0 and 1.", "answer": 0.12831241283124128}
{"qid": "easy-0100", "question_type": "5", "question": "Which 5 authors had the most publications where the titles contain 'Large Language Models' amongst the first 1300 papers at NeurIPS? In the authors column of the database, each entry is a list, not a single string. Return as a list of authors.", "answer": ["Yuan Cao", "Lintang Sutawika", "Subbarao Kambhampati", "Sarath Sreedharan", "Karthik Valmeekam"]}
{"qid": "easy-0101", "question_type": "1", "question": "What was the average time between the filing and issuance of patents from 2006 to 2007? Return an integer representing the number of days by truncating the decimal part.", "answer": 1358}
{"qid": "easy-0102", "question_type": "3", "question": "How does the number of patent applications filed in 2007 compare proportionally to those filed in the 2011? Return a number between 0 and 1. Please note that each row represents a unique patent application, and not all patent applications are assigned a patent number.", "answer": 0.38716814159292035}
{"qid": "easy-0103", "question_type": "3", "question": "How does the number of patent applications filed in 2004 compare proportionally to those filed in the 2006? Return a number between 0 and 1. Please note that each row represents a unique patent application, and not all patent applications are assigned a patent number.", "answer": 4.787866108786611}
{"qid": "easy-0104", "question_type": "6", "question": "What's the ratio of NeurIPS papers that have fewer than or equal to 9 authors? In the authors column of the database, each entry is a list, not a single string. Return a value between 0 and 1.", "answer": 0.9497907949790795}
{"qid": "easy-0105", "question_type": "2", "question": "Which CPC categories were among the top 2 with the highest number of accepted patents in 2014? Return the top categories with the highest approval rates as a list of CPC categories.", "answer": ["H04", "G06"]}
{"qid": "easy-0106", "question_type": "3", "question": "How does the number of patent applications filed in 2014 compare proportionally to those filed in the 2018? Return a number between 0 and 1. Please note that each row represents a unique patent application, and not all patent applications are assigned a patent number.", "answer": 0.3206176203451408}
{"qid": "easy-0107", "question_type": "4", "question": "What is the title of the patent filed between 2010 and 2017 that took the longest number of days between the filing date and the publication date?", "answer": ["EVALUATING KEYWORD PERFORMANCE"]}
{"qid": "easy-0108", "question_type": "1", "question": "What was the typical time span between the submission and approval of patents from 2015 to 2018? Return an integer representing the number of days by truncating the decimal part.", "answer": 565}
{"qid": "easy-0109", "question_type": "1", "question": "What was the typical time span between the submission and approval of patents from 2010 to 2016? Return an integer representing the number of days by truncating the decimal part.", "answer": 852}
{"qid": "easy-0110", "question_type": "3", "question": "How does the number of patent applications filed in 2009 compare proportionally to those filed in the 2015? Return a number between 0 and 1. Please note that each row represents a unique patent application, and not all patent applications are assigned a patent number.", "answer": 0.2051516258677384}
{"qid": "easy-0111", "question_type": "2", "question": "What were the top 2 CPC categories with the highest number of accepted patents in 2016? Return them as a list of CPC categories.", "answer": ["H04", "H01"]}
{"qid": "easy-0112", "question_type": "2", "question": "What were the top 2 CPC categories with the highest number of accepted patents in 2013? Return them as a list of CPC categories.", "answer": ["H04", "G06"]}
{"qid": "easy-0113", "question_type": "5", "question": "Who were the top 4 authors with the highest number of publications where the titles contain 'Large Language Models' amongst the first 2900 papers at NeurIPS? In the authors column of the database, each entry is a list, not a single string. Return as a list of authors.", "answer": ["Sarath Sreedharan", "Karthik Valmeekam", "William Yang Wang", "Subbarao Kambhampati"]}
{"qid": "easy-0114", "question_type": "5", "question": "Who were the top 2 authors with the most publications amongst the first 1500 papers at NeurIPS? In the authors column of the database, each entry is a list, not a single string. Return as a list of authors.", "answer": ["Bernhard Schölkopf", "Mihaela van der Schaar"]}
{"qid": "easy-0115", "question_type": "4", "question": "What is the title of the patent filed between 2009 and 2011 with the longest number of days elapsed between the filing date and the publication date?", "answer": ["DYNAMIC TISSUE HOLDING DEVICE WITH LOW PROFILE SPRING"]}
{"qid": "easy-0116", "question_type": "1", "question": "What was the average time between the filing and issuance of patents from 2006 to 2009? Return an integer representing the number of days by truncating the decimal part.", "answer": 1319}
{"qid": "easy-0117", "question_type": "6", "question": "What percentage of NeurIPS papers have fewer than 5 authors? In the authors column of the database, each entry is a list, not a single string. Return a value between 0 and 1.", "answer": 0.5101813110181311}
{"qid": "easy-0118", "question_type": "4", "question": "What is the title of the patent filed between 2004 and 2005 that took the longest number of days between the filing date and the publication date?", "answer": ["Preserving document construct fidelity in converting graphic-represented documents into text-readable documents"]}
{"qid": "easy-0119", "question_type": "4", "question": "What is the title of the patent filed between 2006 and 2011 that had the longest publication delay in terms of number of days between the filing date and the publication date?", "answer": ["FUEL CARTRIDGE AND FUEL CELL USING THE SAME"]}
{"qid": "easy-0120", "question_type": "5", "question": "Which 4 authors had the most publications where the titles contain 'Large Language Models' amongst the first 3100 papers at NeurIPS? In the authors column of the database, each entry is a list, not a single string. Return as a list of authors.", "answer": ["Subbarao Kambhampati", "William Yang Wang", "Karthik Valmeekam", "Sarath Sreedharan"]}
{"qid": "easy-0121", "question_type": "1", "question": "What was the average duration between the filing and issuance of patents from 2010 to 2012? Return an integer representing the number of days by truncating the decimal part.", "answer": 1042}
{"qid": "easy-0122", "question_type": "4", "question": "What is the title of the patent filed between 2004 and 2014 with the longest number of days elapsed between the filing date and the publication date?", "answer": ["Preserving document construct fidelity in converting graphic-represented documents into text-readable documents"]}
{"qid": "easy-0123", "question_type": "1", "question": "What was the average duration between the filing and issuance of patents from 2014 to 2018? Return an integer representing the number of days by truncating the decimal part.", "answer": 683}
{"qid": "easy-0124", "question_type": "2", "question": "Which IPCR categories were among the top 2 with the highest number of accepted patents in 2007? Return the top categories with the highest approval rates as a list of IPCR categories.", "answer": ["G06", "H04"]}
{"qid": "easy-0125", "question_type": "2", "question": "What were the top 2 IPCR categories with the highest number of accepted patents in 2011? Return them as a list of IPCR categories.", "answer": ["G06", "H04"]}
{"qid": "easy-0126", "question_type": "6", "question": "What proportion of NeurIPS papers have fewer than or equal to 10 authors? In the authors column of the database, each entry is a list, not a single string. Return a value between 0 and 1.", "answer": 0.9656903765690377}
{"qid": "easy-0127", "question_type": "3", "question": "How does the number of patent applications filed in 2007 compare proportionally to those filed in the 2016? Return a number between 0 and 1. Please note that each row represents a unique patent application, and not all patent applications are assigned a patent number.", "answer": 0.2075457712549107}
{"qid": "easy-0128", "question_type": "1", "question": "What was the average time between the filing and issuance of patents from 2005 to 2006? Return an integer representing the number of days by truncating the decimal part.", "answer": 1331}
{"qid": "easy-0129", "question_type": "4", "question": "What is the title of the patent filed between 2005 and 2010 that took the longest number of days between the filing date and the publication date?", "answer": ["FUEL CARTRIDGE AND FUEL CELL USING THE SAME"]}
{"qid": "easy-0130", "question_type": "2", "question": "What were the top 2 IPCR categories with the highest number of accepted patents in 2009? Return them as a list of IPCR categories.", "answer": ["G06", "H04"]}
{"qid": "easy-0131", "question_type": "6", "question": "What percentage of NeurIPS papers have fewer than or equal to 2 authors? In the authors column of the database, each entry is a list, not a single string. Return a value between 0 and 1.", "answer": 0.1087866108786611}
{"qid": "easy-0132", "question_type": "3", "question": "How does the number of patent applications filed in 2005 compare proportionally to those filed in the 2004? Return a number between 0 and 1. Please note that each row represents a unique patent application, and not all patent applications are assigned a patent number.", "answer": 0.24862361268898017}
{"qid": "easy-0133", "question_type": "5", "question": "Who were the top 5 authors with the most publications where the titles contain 'Large Language Models' amongst the first 2200 papers at NeurIPS? In the authors column of the database, each entry is a list, not a single string. Return as a list of authors.", "answer": ["Karthik Valmeekam", "Sarath Sreedharan", "Subbarao Kambhampati", "Yuan Cao", "Lintang Sutawika"]}
{"qid": "easy-0134", "question_type": "6", "question": "What percentage of NeurIPS papers have fewer than or equal to 5 authors? In the authors column of the database, each entry is a list, not a single string. Return a value between 0 and 1.", "answer": 0.6728033472803348}
{"qid": "easy-0135", "question_type": "4", "question": "What is the title of the patent filed between 2016 and 2017 with the longest number of days elapsed between the filing date and the publication date?", "answer": ["System and method for sterilizing and/or deimmunizing an object"]}
{"qid": "easy-0136", "question_type": "4", "question": "What is the title of the patent filed between 2015 and 2016 that took the longest number of days between the filing date and the publication date?", "answer": ["BEARING CENTERING SPRING WITH INTEGRAL OUTER RINGS"]}
{"qid": "easy-0137", "question_type": "3", "question": "How does the number of patent applications filed in 2008 compare proportionally to those filed in the 2016? Return a number between 0 and 1. Please note that each row represents a unique patent application, and not all patent applications are assigned a patent number.", "answer": 0.13275517011340893}
{"qid": "easy-0138", "question_type": "1", "question": "What was the average time between the filing and issuance of patents from 2008 to 2015? Return an integer representing the number of days by truncating the decimal part.", "answer": 930}
{"qid": "easy-0139", "question_type": "1", "question": "What was the average time between the filing and issuance of patents from 2007 to 2012? Return an integer representing the number of days by truncating the decimal part.", "answer": 1131}
{"qid": "easy-0140", "question_type": "3", "question": "How does the number of patent applications filed in 2007 compare proportionally to those filed in the 2009? Return a number between 0 and 1. Please note that each row represents a unique patent application, and not all patent applications are assigned a patent number.", "answer": 2.4933214603739984}
{"qid": "easy-0141", "question_type": "1", "question": "What was the typical time span between the submission and approval of patents from 2005 to 2015? Return an integer representing the number of days by truncating the decimal part.", "answer": 994}
{"qid": "easy-0142", "question_type": "1", "question": "What was the typical time span between the submission and approval of patents from 2017 to 2018? Return an integer representing the number of days by truncating the decimal part.", "answer": 314}
{"qid": "easy-0143", "question_type": "3", "question": "How does the number of patent applications filed in 2010 compare proportionally to those filed in the 2009? Return a number between 0 and 1. Please note that each row represents a unique patent application, and not all patent applications are assigned a patent number.", "answer": 0.9884238646482636}
{"qid": "easy-0144", "question_type": "6", "question": "What percentage of NeurIPS papers have exactly 4 authors? In the authors column of the database, each entry is a list, not a single string. Return a value between 0 and 1.", "answer": 0.21311018131101814}
{"qid": "easy-0145", "question_type": "4", "question": "What is the title of the patent filed between 2017 and 2017 that took the longest number of days between the filing date and the publication date?", "answer": ["NUCLEIC ACID COMPOUNDS FOR BINDING GROWTH DIFFERENTIATION FACTOR 11"]}
{"qid": "easy-0146", "question_type": "2", "question": "What were the top 2 IPCR categories with the highest number of accepted patents in 2008? Return them as a list of IPCR categories.", "answer": ["G06", "H04"]}
{"qid": "easy-0147", "question_type": "1", "question": "What was the average time between the filing and issuance of patents from 2013 to 2017? Return an integer representing the number of days by truncating the decimal part.", "answer": 769}
{"qid": "easy-0148", "question_type": "1", "question": "What was the typical time span between the submission and approval of patents from 2004 to 2013? Return an integer representing the number of days by truncating the decimal part.", "answer": 1138}
{"qid": "easy-0149", "question_type": "1", "question": "What was the average time between the filing and issuance of patents from 2006 to 2012? Return an integer representing the number of days by truncating the decimal part.", "answer": 1157}
{"qid": "easy-0150", "question_type": "6", "question": "What proportion of NeurIPS papers have exactly 2 authors? In the authors column of the database, each entry is a list, not a single string. Return a value between 0 and 1.", "answer": 0.100697350069735}
{"qid": "easy-0151", "question_type": "4", "question": "What is the title of the patent filed between 2015 and 2017 that had the longest publication delay in terms of number of days between the filing date and the publication date?", "answer": ["BEARING CENTERING SPRING WITH INTEGRAL OUTER RINGS"]}
{"qid": "easy-0152", "question_type": "4", "question": "What is the title of the patent filed between 2013 and 2017 that took the longest number of days between the filing date and the publication date?", "answer": ["METHOD FOR ELIMINATING RADIOACTIVE IODINE AND HYDROPHILIC RESIN FOR ELIMINATING RADIOACTIVE IODINE"]}
{"qid": "easy-0153", "question_type": "3", "question": "How does the number of patent applications filed in 2016 compare proportionally to those filed in the 2006? Return a number between 0 and 1. Please note that each row represents a unique patent application, and not all patent applications are assigned a patent number.", "answer": 5.644769874476988}
{"qid": "easy-0154", "question_type": "6", "question": "What percentage of NeurIPS papers have fewer than or equal to 2 authors? In the authors column of the database, each entry is a list, not a single string. Return a value between 0 and 1.", "answer": 0.1087866108786611}
{"qid": "easy-0155", "question_type": "4", "question": "What is the title of the patent filed between 2011 and 2014 with the longest number of days elapsed between the filing date and the publication date?", "answer": ["EVALUATING KEYWORD PERFORMANCE"]}
{"qid": "easy-0156", "question_type": "2", "question": "What were the top 2 IPCR categories with the highest number of accepted patents in 2008? Return them as a list of IPCR categories.", "answer": ["G06", "H04"]}
{"qid": "easy-0157", "question_type": "6", "question": "What percentage of NeurIPS papers have exactly 2 authors? In the authors column of the database, each entry is a list, not a single string. Return a value between 0 and 1.", "answer": 0.100697350069735}
{"qid": "easy-0158", "question_type": "4", "question": "What is the title of the patent filed between 2015 and 2016 with the longest number of days elapsed between the filing date and the publication date?", "answer": ["BEARING CENTERING SPRING WITH INTEGRAL OUTER RINGS"]}
{"qid": "easy-0159", "question_type": "1", "question": "What was the typical time span between the submission and approval of patents from 2014 to 2018? Return an integer representing the number of days by truncating the decimal part.", "answer": 683}
{"qid": "easy-0160", "question_type": "3", "question": "How does the number of patent applications filed in 2018 compare proportionally to those filed in the 2010? Return a number between 0 and 1. Please note that each row represents a unique patent application, and not all patent applications are assigned a patent number.", "answer": 28.764864864864865}
{"qid": "easy-0161", "question_type": "2", "question": "What were the top 2 CPC categories with the highest number of accepted patents in 2012? Return them as a list of CPC categories.", "answer": ["H04", "G06"]}
{"qid": "easy-0162", "question_type": "6", "question": "What's the ratio of NeurIPS papers that have fewer than 9 authors? In the authors column of the database, each entry is a list, not a single string. Return a value between 0 and 1.", "answer": 0.9232914923291492}
{"qid": "easy-0163", "question_type": "5", "question": "Which 4 authors had the most publications where the titles contain 'Large Language Models' amongst the first 3200 papers at NeurIPS? In the authors column of the database, each entry is a list, not a single string. Return as a list of authors.", "answer": ["Karthik Valmeekam", "William Yang Wang", "Sarath Sreedharan", "Subbarao Kambhampati"]}
{"qid": "easy-0164", "question_type": "3", "question": "How does the number of patent applications filed in 2014 compare proportionally to those filed in the 2008? Return a number between 0 and 1. Please note that each row represents a unique patent application, and not all patent applications are assigned a patent number.", "answer": 5.715801228364042}
{"qid": "easy-0165", "question_type": "4", "question": "What is the title of the patent filed between 2012 and 2014 that took the longest number of days between the filing date and the publication date?", "answer": ["EVALUATING KEYWORD PERFORMANCE"]}
{"qid": "easy-0166", "question_type": "3", "question": "How does the number of patent applications filed in 2017 compare proportionally to those filed in the 2016? Return a number between 0 and 1. Please note that each row represents a unique patent application, and not all patent applications are assigned a patent number.", "answer": 0.8221777481283818}
{"qid": "easy-0167", "question_type": "1", "question": "What was the average duration between the filing and issuance of patents from 2012 to 2014? Return an integer representing the number of days by truncating the decimal part.", "answer": 886}
{"qid": "easy-0168", "question_type": "6", "question": "What's the ratio of NeurIPS papers that have fewer than 4 authors? In the authors column of the database, each entry is a list, not a single string. Return a value between 0 and 1.", "answer": 0.29707112970711297}
{"qid": "easy-0169", "question_type": "2", "question": "What were the top 3 CPC categories with the highest number of accepted patents in 2018? Return them as a list of CPC categories.", "answer": ["H04", "A61", "G06"]}
{"qid": "easy-0170", "question_type": "4", "question": "What is the title of the patent filed between 2008 and 2011 that had the longest publication delay in terms of number of days between the filing date and the publication date?", "answer": ["FUEL CARTRIDGE AND FUEL CELL USING THE SAME"]}
{"qid": "easy-0171", "question_type": "2", "question": "Which IPCR categories were among the top 2 with the highest number of accepted patents in 2016? Return the top categories with the highest approval rates as a list of IPCR categories.", "answer": ["H04", "H01"]}
{"qid": "easy-0172", "question_type": "5", "question": "Which 5 authors had the most publications where the titles contain 'Large Language Models' amongst the first 2400 papers at NeurIPS? In the authors column of the database, each entry is a list, not a single string. Return as a list of authors.", "answer": ["Yuan Cao", "Karthik Valmeekam", "Sarath Sreedharan", "Subbarao Kambhampati", "Lintang Sutawika"]}
{"qid": "easy-0173", "question_type": "5", "question": "Who were the top 2 authors with the most publications amongst the first 1900 papers at NeurIPS? In the authors column of the database, each entry is a list, not a single string. Return as a list of authors.", "answer": ["Bernhard Schölkopf", "Bo Li"]}
{"qid": "easy-0174", "question_type": "2", "question": "Which CPC categories were among the top 2 with the highest number of accepted patents in 2015? Return the top categories with the highest approval rates as a list of CPC categories.", "answer": ["H04", "H01"]}
{"qid": "easy-0175", "question_type": "4", "question": "What is the title of the patent filed between 2014 and 2014 that had the longest publication delay in terms of number of days between the filing date and the publication date?", "answer": ["METHOD FOR ELIMINATING RADIOACTIVE IODINE AND HYDROPHILIC RESIN FOR ELIMINATING RADIOACTIVE IODINE"]}
{"qid": "easy-0176", "question_type": "1", "question": "What was the average duration between the filing and issuance of patents from 2012 to 2016? Return an integer representing the number of days by truncating the decimal part.", "answer": 801}
{"qid": "easy-0177", "question_type": "5", "question": "Who were the top 3 authors with the highest number of publications amongst the first 2800 papers at NeurIPS? In the authors column of the database, each entry is a list, not a single string. Return as a list of authors.", "answer": ["Ludwig Schmidt", "Bo Li", "Bo Han"]}
{"qid": "easy-0178", "question_type": "3", "question": "How does the number of patent applications filed in 2016 compare proportionally to those filed in the 2004? Return a number between 0 and 1. Please note that each row represents a unique patent application, and not all patent applications are assigned a patent number.", "answer": 1.1789740452678494}
{"qid": "easy-0179", "question_type": "4", "question": "What is the title of the patent filed between 2005 and 2014 that took the longest number of days between the filing date and the publication date?", "answer": ["FUEL CARTRIDGE AND FUEL CELL USING THE SAME"]}
{"qid": "easy-0180", "question_type": "4", "question": "What is the title of the patent filed between 2012 and 2017 that had the longest publication delay in terms of number of days between the filing date and the publication date?", "answer": ["EVALUATING KEYWORD PERFORMANCE"]}
{"qid": "easy-0181", "question_type": "4", "question": "What is the title of the patent filed between 2006 and 2013 with the longest number of days elapsed between the filing date and the publication date?", "answer": ["FUEL CARTRIDGE AND FUEL CELL USING THE SAME"]}
{"qid": "easy-0182", "question_type": "5", "question": "Who were the top 5 authors with the most publications where the titles contain 'Large Language Models' amongst the first 2000 papers at NeurIPS? In the authors column of the database, each entry is a list, not a single string. Return as a list of authors.", "answer": ["Sarath Sreedharan", "Karthik Valmeekam", "Lintang Sutawika", "Yuan Cao", "Subbarao Kambhampati"]}
{"qid": "easy-0183", "question_type": "2", "question": "What were the top 2 IPCR categories with the highest number of accepted patents in 2018? Return them as a list of IPCR categories.", "answer": ["H04", "A61"]}
{"qid": "easy-0184", "question_type": "1", "question": "What was the average time between the filing and issuance of patents from 2012 to 2014? Return an integer representing the number of days by truncating the decimal part.", "answer": 886}
{"qid": "easy-0185", "question_type": "1", "question": "What was the average time between the filing and issuance of patents from 2008 to 2017? Return an integer representing the number of days by truncating the decimal part.", "answer": 859}
{"qid": "easy-0186", "question_type": "4", "question": "What is the title of the patent filed between 2008 and 2010 that had the longest publication delay in terms of number of days between the filing date and the publication date?", "answer": ["FUEL CARTRIDGE AND FUEL CELL USING THE SAME"]}
{"qid": "easy-0187", "question_type": "1", "question": "What was the average time between the filing and issuance of patents from 2014 to 2014? Return an integer representing the number of days by truncating the decimal part.", "answer": 836}
{"qid": "easy-0188", "question_type": "4", "question": "What is the title of the patent filed between 2011 and 2013 that had the longest publication delay in terms of number of days between the filing date and the publication date?", "answer": ["EVALUATING KEYWORD PERFORMANCE"]}
{"qid": "easy-0189", "question_type": "1", "question": "What was the average duration between the filing and issuance of patents from 2007 to 2011? Return an integer representing the number of days by truncating the decimal part.", "answer": 1159}
{"qid": "easy-0190", "question_type": "6", "question": "What's the ratio of NeurIPS papers that have more than 3 authors? In the authors column of the database, each entry is a list, not a single string. Return a value between 0 and 1.", "answer": 0.702928870292887}
{"qid": "easy-0191", "question_type": "1", "question": "What was the average duration between the filing and issuance of patents from 2013 to 2018? Return an integer representing the number of days by truncating the decimal part.", "answer": 764}
{"qid": "easy-0192", "question_type": "5", "question": "Who were the top 5 authors with the highest number of publications where the titles contain 'Large Language Models' amongst the first 2200 papers at NeurIPS? In the authors column of the database, each entry is a list, not a single string. Return as a list of authors.", "answer": ["Karthik Valmeekam", "Sarath Sreedharan", "Subbarao Kambhampati", "Yuan Cao", "Lintang Sutawika"]}
{"qid": "easy-0193", "question_type": "2", "question": "Which IPCR categories were among the top 2 with the highest number of accepted patents in 2005? Return the top categories with the highest approval rates as a list of IPCR categories.", "answer": ["G06", "H04"]}
{"qid": "easy-0194", "question_type": "4", "question": "What is the title of the patent filed between 2004 and 2011 that had the longest publication delay in terms of number of days between the filing date and the publication date?", "answer": ["Preserving document construct fidelity in converting graphic-represented documents into text-readable documents"]}
{"qid": "easy-0195", "question_type": "5", "question": "Who were the top 5 authors with the highest number of publications where the titles contain 'Large Language Models' amongst the first 2100 papers at NeurIPS? In the authors column of the database, each entry is a list, not a single string. Return as a list of authors.", "answer": ["Sarath Sreedharan", "Karthik Valmeekam", "Lintang Sutawika", "Yuan Cao", "Subbarao Kambhampati"]}
{"qid": "easy-0196", "question_type": "2", "question": "What were the top 2 IPCR categories with the highest number of accepted patents in 2010? Return them as a list of IPCR categories.", "answer": ["G06", "H04"]}
{"qid": "easy-0197", "question_type": "4", "question": "What is the title of the patent filed between 2004 and 2013 that had the longest publication delay in terms of number of days between the filing date and the publication date?", "answer": ["Preserving document construct fidelity in converting graphic-represented documents into text-readable documents"]}
{"qid": "easy-0198", "question_type": "4", "question": "What is the title of the patent filed between 2014 and 2015 with the longest number of days elapsed between the filing date and the publication date?", "answer": ["METHOD FOR ELIMINATING RADIOACTIVE IODINE AND HYDROPHILIC RESIN FOR ELIMINATING RADIOACTIVE IODINE"]}
{"qid": "easy-0199", "question_type": "3", "question": "How does the number of patent applications filed in 2011 compare proportionally to those filed in the 2006? Return a number between 0 and 1. Please note that each row represents a unique patent application, and not all patent applications are assigned a patent number.", "answer": 3.0259414225941423}
{"qid": "easy-0200", "question_type": "2", "question": "Which CPC categories were among the top 3 with the highest number of accepted patents in 2011? Return the top categories with the highest approval rates as a list of CPC categories.", "answer": ["H01", "G01", "H04"]}
{"qid": "easy-0201", "question_type": "3", "question": "How does the number of patent applications filed in 2011 compare proportionally to those filed in the 2016? Return a number between 0 and 1. Please note that each row represents a unique patent application, and not all patent applications are assigned a patent number.", "answer": 0.5360610777555407}
{"qid": "easy-0202", "question_type": "4", "question": "What is the title of the patent filed between 2011 and 2016 with the longest number of days elapsed between the filing date and the publication date?", "answer": ["EVALUATING KEYWORD PERFORMANCE"]}
{"qid": "easy-0203", "question_type": "1", "question": "What was the average duration between the filing and issuance of patents from 2005 to 2013? Return an integer representing the number of days by truncating the decimal part.", "answer": 1079}
{"qid": "easy-0204", "question_type": "2", "question": "What were the top 2 CPC categories with the highest number of accepted patents in 2017? Return them as a list of CPC categories.", "answer": ["H01", "H04"]}
{"qid": "easy-0205", "question_type": "1", "question": "What was the average time between the filing and issuance of patents from 2011 to 2011? Return an integer representing the number of days by truncating the decimal part.", "answer": 1054}
{"qid": "easy-0206", "question_type": "3", "question": "How does the number of patent applications filed in 2011 compare proportionally to those filed in the 2005? Return a number between 0 and 1. Please note that each row represents a unique patent application, and not all patent applications are assigned a patent number.", "answer": 2.5420035149384885}
{"qid": "easy-0207", "question_type": "4", "question": "What is the title of the patent filed between 2012 and 2017 with the longest number of days elapsed between the filing date and the publication date?", "answer": ["EVALUATING KEYWORD PERFORMANCE"]}
{"qid": "easy-0208", "question_type": "3", "question": "How does the number of patent applications filed in 2014 compare proportionally to those filed in the 2016? Return a number between 0 and 1. Please note that each row represents a unique patent application, and not all patent applications are assigned a patent number.", "answer": 0.7588021644059002}
{"qid": "easy-0209", "question_type": "6", "question": "What's the ratio of NeurIPS papers that have fewer than or equal to 5 authors? In the authors column of the database, each entry is a list, not a single string. Return a value between 0 and 1.", "answer": 0.6728033472803348}
{"qid": "easy-0210", "question_type": "4", "question": "What is the title of the patent filed between 2012 and 2014 that took the longest number of days between the filing date and the publication date?", "answer": ["EVALUATING KEYWORD PERFORMANCE"]}
{"qid": "easy-0211", "question_type": "5", "question": "Who were the top 5 authors with the highest number of publications where the titles contain 'Large Language Models' amongst the first 1800 papers at NeurIPS? In the authors column of the database, each entry is a list, not a single string. Return as a list of authors.", "answer": ["Karthik Valmeekam", "Lintang Sutawika", "Yuan Cao", "Sarath Sreedharan", "Subbarao Kambhampati"]}
{"qid": "easy-0212", "question_type": "4", "question": "What is the title of the patent filed between 2004 and 2015 that had the longest publication delay in terms of number of days between the filing date and the publication date?", "answer": ["Preserving document construct fidelity in converting graphic-represented documents into text-readable documents"]}
{"qid": "easy-0213", "question_type": "3", "question": "How does the number of patent applications filed in 2015 compare proportionally to those filed in the 2008? Return a number between 0 and 1. Please note that each row represents a unique patent application, and not all patent applications are assigned a patent number.", "answer": 3.056393076493579}
{"qid": "easy-0214", "question_type": "4", "question": "What is the title of the patent filed between 2004 and 2015 that took the longest number of days between the filing date and the publication date?", "answer": ["Preserving document construct fidelity in converting graphic-represented documents into text-readable documents"]}
{"qid": "easy-0215", "question_type": "6", "question": "What proportion of NeurIPS papers have greater than or equal to 5 authors? In the authors column of the database, each entry is a list, not a single string. Return a value between 0 and 1.", "answer": 0.4898186889818689}
{"qid": "easy-0216", "question_type": "6", "question": "What percentage of NeurIPS papers have more than 3 authors? In the authors column of the database, each entry is a list, not a single string. Return a value between 0 and 1.", "answer": 0.702928870292887}
{"qid": "easy-0217", "question_type": "5", "question": "Which 4 authors had the most publications where the titles contain 'Large Language Models' amongst the first 2900 papers at NeurIPS? In the authors column of the database, each entry is a list, not a single string. Return as a list of authors.", "answer": ["Sarath Sreedharan", "Karthik Valmeekam", "William Yang Wang", "Subbarao Kambhampati"]}
{"qid": "easy-0218", "question_type": "1", "question": "What was the average time between the filing and issuance of patents from 2017 to 2018? Return an integer representing the number of days by truncating the decimal part.", "answer": 314}
{"qid": "easy-0219", "question_type": "4", "question": "What is the title of the patent filed between 2011 and 2014 that had the longest publication delay in terms of number of days between the filing date and the publication date?", "answer": ["EVALUATING KEYWORD PERFORMANCE"]}
{"qid": "easy-0220", "question_type": "2", "question": "What were the top 2 IPCR categories with the highest number of accepted patents in 2008? Return them as a list of IPCR categories.", "answer": ["G06", "H04"]}
{"qid": "easy-0221", "question_type": "6", "question": "What's the ratio of NeurIPS papers that have fewer than 4 authors? In the authors column of the database, each entry is a list, not a single string. Return a value between 0 and 1.", "answer": 0.29707112970711297}
{"qid": "easy-0222", "question_type": "2", "question": "What were the top 2 IPCR categories with the highest number of accepted patents in 2007? Return them as a list of IPCR categories.", "answer": ["G06", "H04"]}
{"qid": "easy-0223", "question_type": "1", "question": "What was the average duration between the filing and issuance of patents from 2017 to 2017? Return an integer representing the number of days by truncating the decimal part.", "answer": 343}
{"qid": "easy-0224", "question_type": "3", "question": "How does the number of patent applications filed in 2018 compare proportionally to those filed in the 2015? Return a number between 0 and 1. Please note that each row represents a unique patent application, and not all patent applications are assigned a patent number.", "answer": 5.832846181951041}
{"qid": "easy-0225", "question_type": "1", "question": "What was the typical time span between the submission and approval of patents from 2017 to 2018? Return an integer representing the number of days by truncating the decimal part.", "answer": 314}
{"qid": "easy-0226", "question_type": "2", "question": "Which IPCR categories were among the top 2 with the highest number of accepted patents in 2008? Return the top categories with the highest approval rates as a list of IPCR categories.", "answer": ["G06", "H04"]}
{"qid": "easy-0227", "question_type": "4", "question": "What is the title of the patent filed between 2007 and 2009 that took the longest number of days between the filing date and the publication date?", "answer": ["FUEL CARTRIDGE AND FUEL CELL USING THE SAME"]}
{"qid": "easy-0228", "question_type": "3", "question": "How does the number of patent applications filed in 2012 compare proportionally to those filed in the 2011? Return a number between 0 and 1. Please note that each row represents a unique patent application, and not all patent applications are assigned a patent number.", "answer": 0.3073838495575221}
{"qid": "easy-0229", "question_type": "5", "question": "Which 5 authors had the most publications where the titles contain 'Large Language Models' amongst the first 2400 papers at NeurIPS? In the authors column of the database, each entry is a list, not a single string. Return as a list of authors.", "answer": ["Yuan Cao", "Karthik Valmeekam", "Sarath Sreedharan", "Subbarao Kambhampati", "Lintang Sutawika"]}
{"qid": "easy-0230", "question_type": "2", "question": "What were the top 2 CPC categories with the highest number of accepted patents in 2014? Return them as a list of CPC categories.", "answer": ["H04", "G06"]}
{"qid": "easy-0231", "question_type": "6", "question": "What's the ratio of NeurIPS papers that have greater than or equal to 5 authors? In the authors column of the database, each entry is a list, not a single string. Return a value between 0 and 1.", "answer": 0.4898186889818689}
{"qid": "easy-0232", "question_type": "3", "question": "How does the number of patent applications filed in 2016 compare proportionally to those filed in the 2006? Return a number between 0 and 1. Please note that each row represents a unique patent application, and not all patent applications are assigned a patent number.", "answer": 5.644769874476988}
{"qid": "easy-0233", "question_type": "5", "question": "Who were the top 3 authors with the highest number of publications where the titles contain 'Large Language Models' amongst the first 2600 papers at NeurIPS? In the authors column of the database, each entry is a list, not a single string. Return as a list of authors.", "answer": ["Karthik Valmeekam", "Sarath Sreedharan", "Subbarao Kambhampati"]}
{"qid": "easy-0234", "question_type": "1", "question": "What was the average time between the filing and issuance of patents from 2011 to 2016? Return an integer representing the number of days by truncating the decimal part.", "answer": 845}
{"qid": "easy-0235", "question_type": "6", "question": "What percentage of NeurIPS papers have exactly 6 authors? In the authors column of the database, each entry is a list, not a single string. Return a value between 0 and 1.", "answer": 0.1199442119944212}
{"qid": "easy-0236", "question_type": "4", "question": "What is the title of the patent filed between 2015 and 2016 that had the longest publication delay in terms of number of days between the filing date and the publication date?", "answer": ["BEARING CENTERING SPRING WITH INTEGRAL OUTER RINGS"]}
{"qid": "easy-0237", "question_type": "4", "question": "What is the title of the patent filed between 2007 and 2013 that had the longest publication delay in terms of number of days between the filing date and the publication date?", "answer": ["FUEL CARTRIDGE AND FUEL CELL USING THE SAME"]}
{"qid": "easy-0238", "question_type": "1", "question": "What was the typical time span between the submission and approval of patents from 2014 to 2014? Return an integer representing the number of days by truncating the decimal part.", "answer": 836}
{"qid": "easy-0239", "question_type": "3", "question": "How does the number of patent applications filed in 2012 compare proportionally to those filed in the 2008? Return a number between 0 and 1. Please note that each row represents a unique patent application, and not all patent applications are assigned a patent number.", "answer": 1.2412060301507537}
{"qid": "easy-0240", "question_type": "5", "question": "Who were the top 5 authors with the highest number of publications where the titles contain 'Large Language Models' amongst the first 2400 papers at NeurIPS? In the authors column of the database, each entry is a list, not a single string. Return as a list of authors.", "answer": ["Yuan Cao", "Karthik Valmeekam", "Sarath Sreedharan", "Subbarao Kambhampati", "Lintang Sutawika"]}
{"qid": "easy-0241", "question_type": "4", "question": "What is the title of the patent filed between 2005 and 2015 with the longest number of days elapsed between the filing date and the publication date?", "answer": ["FUEL CARTRIDGE AND FUEL CELL USING THE SAME"]}
{"qid": "easy-0242", "question_type": "1", "question": "What was the typical time span between the submission and approval of patents from 2018 to 2018? Return an integer representing the number of days by truncating the decimal part.", "answer": 160}
{"qid": "easy-0243", "question_type": "6", "question": "What's the ratio of NeurIPS papers that have fewer than or equal to 3 authors? In the authors column of the database, each entry is a list, not a single string. Return a value between 0 and 1.", "answer": 0.29707112970711297}
{"qid": "easy-0244", "question_type": "6", "question": "What's the ratio of NeurIPS papers that have fewer than 9 authors? In the authors column of the database, each entry is a list, not a single string. Return a value between 0 and 1.", "answer": 0.9232914923291492}
{"qid": "easy-0245", "question_type": "6", "question": "What proportion of NeurIPS papers have greater than or equal to 2 authors? In the authors column of the database, each entry is a list, not a single string. Return a value between 0 and 1.", "answer": 0.9919107391910739}
{"qid": "easy-0246", "question_type": "3", "question": "How does the number of patent applications filed in 2010 compare proportionally to those filed in the 2017? Return a number between 0 and 1. Please note that each row represents a unique patent application, and not all patent applications are assigned a patent number.", "answer": 0.1000721240533718}
{"qid": "easy-0247", "question_type": "3", "question": "How does the number of patent applications filed in 2010 compare proportionally to those filed in the 2016? Return a number between 0 and 1. Please note that each row represents a unique patent application, and not all patent applications are assigned a patent number.", "answer": 0.0822770736046253}
{"qid": "easy-0248", "question_type": "6", "question": "What's the ratio of NeurIPS papers that have greater than or equal to 8 authors? In the authors column of the database, each entry is a list, not a single string. Return a value between 0 and 1.", "answer": 0.12831241283124128}
{"qid": "easy-0249", "question_type": "2", "question": "Which CPC categories were among the top 2 with the highest number of accepted patents in 2015? Return the top categories with the highest approval rates as a list of CPC categories.", "answer": ["H04", "H01"]}
{"qid": "easy-0250", "question_type": "4", "question": "What is the title of the patent filed between 2010 and 2015 with the longest number of days elapsed between the filing date and the publication date?", "answer": ["EVALUATING KEYWORD PERFORMANCE"]}
{"qid": "easy-0251", "question_type": "5", "question": "Who were the top 5 authors with the highest number of publications where the titles contain 'Large Language Models' amongst the first 2300 papers at NeurIPS? In the authors column of the database, each entry is a list, not a single string. Return as a list of authors.", "answer": ["Yuan Cao", "Karthik Valmeekam", "Sarath Sreedharan", "Subbarao Kambhampati", "Lintang Sutawika"]}
{"qid": "easy-0252", "question_type": "4", "question": "What is the title of the patent filed between 2006 and 2012 that took the longest number of days between the filing date and the publication date?", "answer": ["FUEL CARTRIDGE AND FUEL CELL USING THE SAME"]}
{"qid": "easy-0253", "question_type": "6", "question": "What percentage of NeurIPS papers have more than 9 authors? In the authors column of the database, each entry is a list, not a single string. Return a value between 0 and 1.", "answer": 0.0502092050209205}
{"qid": "easy-0254", "question_type": "2", "question": "What were the top 2 IPCR categories with the highest number of accepted patents in 2013? Return them as a list of IPCR categories.", "answer": ["H04", "G06"]}
{"qid": "easy-0255", "question_type": "2", "question": "Which CPC categories were among the top 2 with the highest number of accepted patents in 2014? Return the top categories with the highest approval rates as a list of CPC categories.", "answer": ["H04", "G06"]}
{"qid": "easy-0256", "question_type": "4", "question": "What is the title of the patent filed between 2007 and 2008 with the longest number of days elapsed between the filing date and the publication date?", "answer": ["FUEL CARTRIDGE AND FUEL CELL USING THE SAME"]}
{"qid": "easy-0257", "question_type": "2", "question": "What were the top 2 IPCR categories with the highest number of accepted patents in 2015? Return them as a list of IPCR categories.", "answer": ["H04", "H01"]}
{"qid": "easy-0258", "question_type": "3", "question": "How does the number of patent applications filed in 2012 compare proportionally to those filed in the 2015? Return a number between 0 and 1. Please note that each row represents a unique patent application, and not all patent applications are assigned a patent number.", "answer": 0.4061015710632079}
{"qid": "easy-0259", "question_type": "6", "question": "What percentage of NeurIPS papers have exactly 4 authors? In the authors column of the database, each entry is a list, not a single string. Return a value between 0 and 1.", "answer": 0.21311018131101814}
{"qid": "easy-0260", "question_type": "1", "question": "What was the typical time span between the submission and approval of patents from 2010 to 2012? Return an integer representing the number of days by truncating the decimal part.", "answer": 1042}
{"qid": "easy-0261", "question_type": "2", "question": "What were the top 2 IPCR categories with the highest number of accepted patents in 2004? Return them as a list of IPCR categories.", "answer": ["G06", "H04"]}
{"qid": "easy-0262", "question_type": "2", "question": "Which CPC categories were among the top 3 with the highest number of accepted patents in 2011? Return the top categories with the highest approval rates as a list of CPC categories.", "answer": ["H01", "G01", "H04"]}
{"qid": "easy-0263", "question_type": "3", "question": "How does the number of patent applications filed in 2014 compare proportionally to those filed in the 2004? Return a number between 0 and 1. Please note that each row represents a unique patent application, and not all patent applications are assigned a patent number.", "answer": 0.8946080573276238}
{"qid": "easy-0264", "question_type": "6", "question": "What percentage of NeurIPS papers have greater than or equal to 5 authors? In the authors column of the database, each entry is a list, not a single string. Return a value between 0 and 1.", "answer": 0.4898186889818689}
{"qid": "easy-0265", "question_type": "1", "question": "What was the average time between the filing and issuance of patents from 2016 to 2017? Return an integer representing the number of days by truncating the decimal part.", "answer": 499}
{"qid": "easy-0266", "question_type": "4", "question": "What is the title of the patent filed between 2015 and 2017 that took the longest number of days between the filing date and the publication date?", "answer": ["BEARING CENTERING SPRING WITH INTEGRAL OUTER RINGS"]}
{"qid": "easy-0267", "question_type": "6", "question": "What percentage of NeurIPS papers have exactly 9 authors? In the authors column of the database, each entry is a list, not a single string. Return a value between 0 and 1.", "answer": 0.026499302649930265}
{"qid": "easy-0268", "question_type": "6", "question": "What percentage of NeurIPS papers have fewer than or equal to 9 authors? In the authors column of the database, each entry is a list, not a single string. Return a value between 0 and 1.", "answer": 0.9497907949790795}
{"qid": "easy-0269", "question_type": "3", "question": "How does the number of patent applications filed in 2009 compare proportionally to those filed in the 2011? Return a number between 0 and 1. Please note that each row represents a unique patent application, and not all patent applications are assigned a patent number.", "answer": 0.1552820796460177}
{"qid": "easy-0270", "question_type": "3", "question": "How does the number of patent applications filed in 2017 compare proportionally to those filed in the 2004? Return a number between 0 and 1. Please note that each row represents a unique patent application, and not all patent applications are assigned a patent number.", "answer": 0.9693262256401294}
{"qid": "easy-0271", "question_type": "3", "question": "How does the number of patent applications filed in 2011 compare proportionally to those filed in the 2005? Return a number between 0 and 1. Please note that each row represents a unique patent application, and not all patent applications are assigned a patent number.", "answer": 2.5420035149384885}
{"qid": "easy-0272", "question_type": "6", "question": "What percentage of NeurIPS papers have fewer than 10 authors? In the authors column of the database, each entry is a list, not a single string. Return a value between 0 and 1.", "answer": 0.9497907949790795}
{"qid": "easy-0273", "question_type": "1", "question": "What was the average duration between the filing and issuance of patents from 2004 to 2005? Return an integer representing the number of days by truncating the decimal part.", "answer": 1315}
{"qid": "easy-0274", "question_type": "3", "question": "How does the number of patent applications filed in 2004 compare proportionally to those filed in the 2018? Return a number between 0 and 1. Please note that each row represents a unique patent application, and not all patent applications are assigned a patent number.", "answer": 0.35838892542829404}
{"qid": "easy-0275", "question_type": "6", "question": "What percentage of NeurIPS papers have fewer than or equal to 8 authors? In the authors column of the database, each entry is a list, not a single string. Return a value between 0 and 1.", "answer": 0.9232914923291492}
{"qid": "easy-0276", "question_type": "3", "question": "How does the number of patent applications filed in 2011 compare proportionally to those filed in the 2009? Return a number between 0 and 1. Please note that each row represents a unique patent application, and not all patent applications are assigned a patent number.", "answer": 6.439893143365984}
{"qid": "easy-0277", "question_type": "2", "question": "Which IPCR categories were among the top 2 with the highest number of accepted patents in 2009? Return the top categories with the highest approval rates as a list of IPCR categories.", "answer": ["G06", "H04"]}
{"qid": "easy-0278", "question_type": "1", "question": "What was the typical time span between the submission and approval of patents from 2013 to 2013? Return an integer representing the number of days by truncating the decimal part.", "answer": 912}
{"qid": "easy-0279", "question_type": "4", "question": "What is the title of the patent filed between 2014 and 2015 with the longest number of days elapsed between the filing date and the publication date?", "answer": ["METHOD FOR ELIMINATING RADIOACTIVE IODINE AND HYDROPHILIC RESIN FOR ELIMINATING RADIOACTIVE IODINE"]}
{"qid": "easy-0280", "question_type": "6", "question": "What's the ratio of NeurIPS papers that have more than 8 authors? In the authors column of the database, each entry is a list, not a single string. Return a value between 0 and 1.", "answer": 0.07670850767085077}
{"qid": "easy-0281", "question_type": "6", "question": "What percentage of NeurIPS papers have exactly 7 authors? In the authors column of the database, each entry is a list, not a single string. Return a value between 0 and 1.", "answer": 0.07894002789400278}
{"qid": "easy-0282", "question_type": "4", "question": "What is the title of the patent filed between 2010 and 2013 with the longest number of days elapsed between the filing date and the publication date?", "answer": ["EVALUATING KEYWORD PERFORMANCE"]}
{"qid": "easy-0283", "question_type": "5", "question": "Who were the top 5 authors with the highest number of publications where the titles contain 'Large Language Models' amongst the first 2500 papers at NeurIPS? In the authors column of the database, each entry is a list, not a single string. Return as a list of authors.", "answer": ["Subbarao Kambhampati", "Sarath Sreedharan", "Yuan Cao", "Karthik Valmeekam", "Lintang Sutawika"]}
{"qid": "easy-0284", "question_type": "4", "question": "What is the title of the patent filed between 2017 and 2017 that took the longest number of days between the filing date and the publication date?", "answer": ["NUCLEIC ACID COMPOUNDS FOR BINDING GROWTH DIFFERENTIATION FACTOR 11"]}
{"qid": "easy-0285", "question_type": "6", "question": "What proportion of NeurIPS papers have more than 2 authors? In the authors column of the database, each entry is a list, not a single string. Return a value between 0 and 1.", "answer": 0.891213389121339}
{"qid": "easy-0286", "question_type": "6", "question": "What's the ratio of NeurIPS papers that have fewer than or equal to 3 authors? In the authors column of the database, each entry is a list, not a single string. Return a value between 0 and 1.", "answer": 0.29707112970711297}
{"qid": "easy-0287", "question_type": "3", "question": "How does the number of patent applications filed in 2016 compare proportionally to those filed in the 2008? Return a number between 0 and 1. Please note that each row represents a unique patent application, and not all patent applications are assigned a patent number.", "answer": 7.532663316582915}
{"qid": "easy-0288", "question_type": "6", "question": "What percentage of NeurIPS papers have exactly 6 authors? In the authors column of the database, each entry is a list, not a single string. Return a value between 0 and 1.", "answer": 0.1199442119944212}
{"qid": "easy-0289", "question_type": "2", "question": "What were the top 2 IPCR categories with the highest number of accepted patents in 2016? Return them as a list of IPCR categories.", "answer": ["H04", "H01"]}
{"qid": "easy-0290", "question_type": "5", "question": "Which 5 authors had the most publications where the titles contain 'Large Language Models' amongst the first 2300 papers at NeurIPS? In the authors column of the database, each entry is a list, not a single string. Return as a list of authors.", "answer": ["Yuan Cao", "Karthik Valmeekam", "Sarath Sreedharan", "Subbarao Kambhampati", "Lintang Sutawika"]}
{"qid": "easy-0291", "question_type": "3", "question": "How does the number of patent applications filed in 2010 compare proportionally to those filed in the 2012? Return a number between 0 and 1. Please note that each row represents a unique patent application, and not all patent applications are assigned a patent number.", "answer": 0.4993252361673414}
{"qid": "easy-0292", "question_type": "1", "question": "What was the typical time span between the submission and approval of patents from 2005 to 2012? Return an integer representing the number of days by truncating the decimal part.", "answer": 1177}
{"qid": "easy-0293", "question_type": "6", "question": "What percentage of NeurIPS papers have greater than or equal to 8 authors? In the authors column of the database, each entry is a list, not a single string. Return a value between 0 and 1.", "answer": 0.12831241283124128}
{"qid": "easy-0294", "question_type": "1", "question": "What was the average duration between the filing and issuance of patents from 2004 to 2007? Return an integer representing the number of days by truncating the decimal part.", "answer": 1326}
{"qid": "easy-0295", "question_type": "3", "question": "How does the number of patent applications filed in 2017 compare proportionally to those filed in the 2006? Return a number between 0 and 1. Please note that each row represents a unique patent application, and not all patent applications are assigned a patent number.", "answer": 4.641004184100418}
{"qid": "easy-0296", "question_type": "5", "question": "Who were the top 5 authors with the most publications where the titles contain 'Large Language Models' amongst the first 1700 papers at NeurIPS? In the authors column of the database, each entry is a list, not a single string. Return as a list of authors.", "answer": ["Lintang Sutawika", "Subbarao Kambhampati", "Yuan Cao", "Karthik Valmeekam", "Sarath Sreedharan"]}
{"qid": "easy-0297", "question_type": "1", "question": "What was the average time between the filing and issuance of patents from 2005 to 2015? Return an integer representing the number of days by truncating the decimal part.", "answer": 994}
{"qid": "easy-0298", "question_type": "6", "question": "What's the ratio of NeurIPS papers that have fewer than or equal to 3 authors? In the authors column of the database, each entry is a list, not a single string. Return a value between 0 and 1.", "answer": 0.29707112970711297}
{"qid": "easy-0299", "question_type": "3", "question": "How does the number of patent applications filed in 2011 compare proportionally to those filed in the 2007? Return a number between 0 and 1. Please note that each row represents a unique patent application, and not all patent applications are assigned a patent number.", "answer": 2.5828571428571427}
{"qid": "easy-0300", "question_type": "3", "question": "How does the number of patent applications filed in 2013 compare proportionally to those filed in the 2010? Return a number between 0 and 1. Please note that each row represents a unique patent application, and not all patent applications are assigned a patent number.", "answer": 10.981981981981981}
{"qid": "easy-0301", "question_type": "3", "question": "How does the number of patent applications filed in 2006 compare proportionally to those filed in the 2005? Return a number between 0 and 1. Please note that each row represents a unique patent application, and not all patent applications are assigned a patent number.", "answer": 0.8400702987697716}
{"qid": "easy-0302", "question_type": "6", "question": "What's the ratio of NeurIPS papers that have exactly 5 authors? In the authors column of the database, each entry is a list, not a single string. Return a value between 0 and 1.", "answer": 0.16262203626220362}
{"qid": "easy-0303", "question_type": "6", "question": "What's the ratio of NeurIPS papers that have greater than or equal to 6 authors? In the authors column of the database, each entry is a list, not a single string. Return a value between 0 and 1.", "answer": 0.32719665271966525}
{"qid": "easy-0304", "question_type": "6", "question": "What's the ratio of NeurIPS papers that have fewer than 5 authors? In the authors column of the database, each entry is a list, not a single string. Return a value between 0 and 1.", "answer": 0.5101813110181311}
{"qid": "easy-0305", "question_type": "6", "question": "What's the ratio of NeurIPS papers that have fewer than or equal to 3 authors? In the authors column of the database, each entry is a list, not a single string. Return a value between 0 and 1.", "answer": 0.29707112970711297}
{"qid": "easy-0306", "question_type": "1", "question": "What was the average time between the filing and issuance of patents from 2005 to 2015? Return an integer representing the number of days by truncating the decimal part.", "answer": 994}
{"qid": "easy-0307", "question_type": "6", "question": "What's the ratio of NeurIPS papers that have greater than or equal to 5 authors? In the authors column of the database, each entry is a list, not a single string. Return a value between 0 and 1.", "answer": 0.4898186889818689}
{"qid": "easy-0308", "question_type": "2", "question": "What were the top 2 CPC categories with the highest number of accepted patents in 2013? Return them as a list of CPC categories.", "answer": ["H04", "G06"]}
{"qid": "easy-0309", "question_type": "3", "question": "How does the number of patent applications filed in 2007 compare proportionally to those filed in the 2012? Return a number between 0 and 1. Please note that each row represents a unique patent application, and not all patent applications are assigned a patent number.", "answer": 1.2595591542959963}
{"qid": "easy-0310", "question_type": "1", "question": "What was the average time between the filing and issuance of patents from 2008 to 2018? Return an integer representing the number of days by truncating the decimal part.", "answer": 855}
{"qid": "easy-0311", "question_type": "1", "question": "What was the average time between the filing and issuance of patents from 2018 to 2018? Return an integer representing the number of days by truncating the decimal part.", "answer": 160}
{"qid": "easy-0312", "question_type": "5", "question": "Who were the top 4 authors with the highest number of publications where the titles contain 'Large Language Models' amongst the first 2900 papers at NeurIPS? In the authors column of the database, each entry is a list, not a single string. Return as a list of authors.", "answer": ["Sarath Sreedharan", "Karthik Valmeekam", "William Yang Wang", "Subbarao Kambhampati"]}
{"qid": "easy-0313", "question_type": "1", "question": "What was the typical time span between the submission and approval of patents from 2009 to 2016? Return an integer representing the number of days by truncating the decimal part.", "answer": 861}
{"qid": "easy-0314", "question_type": "4", "question": "What is the title of the patent filed between 2005 and 2009 with the longest number of days elapsed between the filing date and the publication date?", "answer": ["FUEL CARTRIDGE AND FUEL CELL USING THE SAME"]}
{"qid": "easy-0315", "question_type": "4", "question": "What is the title of the patent filed between 2008 and 2014 with the longest number of days elapsed between the filing date and the publication date?", "answer": ["FUEL CARTRIDGE AND FUEL CELL USING THE SAME"]}
{"qid": "easy-0316", "question_type": "1", "question": "What was the average duration between the filing and issuance of patents from 2018 to 2018? Return an integer representing the number of days by truncating the decimal part.", "answer": 160}
{"qid": "easy-0317", "question_type": "3", "question": "How does the number of patent applications filed in 2017 compare proportionally to those filed in the 2011? Return a number between 0 and 1. Please note that each row represents a unique patent application, and not all patent applications are assigned a patent number.", "answer": 1.5337389380530972}
{"qid": "easy-0318", "question_type": "5", "question": "Who were the top 4 authors with the highest number of publications where the titles contain 'Large Language Models' amongst the first 3300 papers at NeurIPS? In the authors column of the database, each entry is a list, not a single string. Return as a list of authors.", "answer": ["William Yang Wang", "Karthik Valmeekam", "Sarath Sreedharan", "Subbarao Kambhampati"]}
{"qid": "easy-0319", "question_type": "5", "question": "Who were the top 5 authors with the highest number of publications where the titles contain 'Large Language Models' amongst the first 2000 papers at NeurIPS? In the authors column of the database, each entry is a list, not a single string. Return as a list of authors.", "answer": ["Sarath Sreedharan", "Karthik Valmeekam", "Lintang Sutawika", "Yuan Cao", "Subbarao Kambhampati"]}
{"qid": "easy-0320", "question_type": "4", "question": "What is the title of the patent filed between 2010 and 2013 that had the longest publication delay in terms of number of days between the filing date and the publication date?", "answer": ["EVALUATING KEYWORD PERFORMANCE"]}
{"qid": "easy-0321", "question_type": "2", "question": "What were the top 2 CPC categories with the highest number of accepted patents in 2015? Return them as a list of CPC categories.", "answer": ["H04", "H01"]}
{"qid": "easy-0322", "question_type": "6", "question": "What percentage of NeurIPS papers have exactly 3 authors? In the authors column of the database, each entry is a list, not a single string. Return a value between 0 and 1.", "answer": 0.18828451882845187}
{"qid": "easy-0323", "question_type": "1", "question": "What was the average time between the filing and issuance of patents from 2008 to 2017? Return an integer representing the number of days by truncating the decimal part.", "answer": 859}
{"qid": "easy-0324", "question_type": "4", "question": "What is the title of the patent filed between 2006 and 2012 that took the longest number of days between the filing date and the publication date?", "answer": ["FUEL CARTRIDGE AND FUEL CELL USING THE SAME"]}
{"qid": "easy-0325", "question_type": "6", "question": "What proportion of NeurIPS papers have greater than or equal to 5 authors? In the authors column of the database, each entry is a list, not a single string. Return a value between 0 and 1.", "answer": 0.4898186889818689}
{"qid": "easy-0326", "question_type": "2", "question": "Which CPC categories were among the top 2 with the highest number of accepted patents in 2017? Return the top categories with the highest approval rates as a list of CPC categories.", "answer": ["H01", "H04"]}
{"qid": "easy-0327", "question_type": "5", "question": "Which 2 authors had the most publications amongst the first 1900 papers at NeurIPS? In the authors column of the database, each entry is a list, not a single string. Return as a list of authors.", "answer": ["Bernhard Schölkopf", "Bo Li"]}
{"qid": "easy-0328", "question_type": "1", "question": "What was the average duration between the filing and issuance of patents from 2009 to 2009? Return an integer representing the number of days by truncating the decimal part.", "answer": 1200}
{"qid": "easy-0329", "question_type": "3", "question": "How does the number of patent applications filed in 2014 compare proportionally to those filed in the 2005? Return a number between 0 and 1. Please note that each row represents a unique patent application, and not all patent applications are assigned a patent number.", "answer": 3.5982425307557118}
{"qid": "easy-0330", "question_type": "4", "question": "What is the title of the patent filed between 2007 and 2008 that had the longest publication delay in terms of number of days between the filing date and the publication date?", "answer": ["FUEL CARTRIDGE AND FUEL CELL USING THE SAME"]}
{"qid": "easy-0331", "question_type": "1", "question": "What was the average duration between the filing and issuance of patents from 2013 to 2015? Return an integer representing the number of days by truncating the decimal part.", "answer": 849}
{"qid": "easy-0332", "question_type": "4", "question": "What is the title of the patent filed between 2005 and 2011 that took the longest number of days between the filing date and the publication date?", "answer": ["FUEL CARTRIDGE AND FUEL CELL USING THE SAME"]}
{"qid": "easy-0333", "question_type": "3", "question": "How does the number of patent applications filed in 2005 compare proportionally to those filed in the 2011? Return a number between 0 and 1. Please note that each row represents a unique patent application, and not all patent applications are assigned a patent number.", "answer": 0.39339048672566373}
{"qid": "easy-0334", "question_type": "4", "question": "What is the title of the patent filed between 2014 and 2015 with the longest number of days elapsed between the filing date and the publication date?", "answer": ["METHOD FOR ELIMINATING RADIOACTIVE IODINE AND HYDROPHILIC RESIN FOR ELIMINATING RADIOACTIVE IODINE"]}
{"qid": "easy-0335", "question_type": "6", "question": "What proportion of NeurIPS papers have exactly 8 authors? In the authors column of the database, each entry is a list, not a single string. Return a value between 0 and 1.", "answer": 0.05160390516039052}
{"qid": "easy-0336", "question_type": "3", "question": "How does the number of patent applications filed in 2007 compare proportionally to those filed in the 2008? Return a number between 0 and 1. Please note that each row represents a unique patent application, and not all patent applications are assigned a patent number.", "answer": 1.5633724176437744}
{"qid": "easy-0337", "question_type": "3", "question": "How does the number of patent applications filed in 2004 compare proportionally to those filed in the 2013? Return a number between 0 and 1. Please note that each row represents a unique patent application, and not all patent applications are assigned a patent number.", "answer": 0.9387202625102543}
{"qid": "easy-0338", "question_type": "4", "question": "What is the title of the patent filed between 2006 and 2017 with the longest number of days elapsed between the filing date and the publication date?", "answer": ["FUEL CARTRIDGE AND FUEL CELL USING THE SAME"]}
{"qid": "easy-0339", "question_type": "4", "question": "What is the title of the patent filed between 2017 and 2017 that took the longest number of days between the filing date and the publication date?", "answer": ["NUCLEIC ACID COMPOUNDS FOR BINDING GROWTH DIFFERENTIATION FACTOR 11"]}
{"qid": "easy-0340", "question_type": "1", "question": "What was the average time between the filing and issuance of patents from 2014 to 2018? Return an integer representing the number of days by truncating the decimal part.", "answer": 683}
{"qid": "easy-0341", "question_type": "1", "question": "What was the average duration between the filing and issuance of patents from 2007 to 2012? Return an integer representing the number of days by truncating the decimal part.", "answer": 1131}
{"qid": "easy-0342", "question_type": "2", "question": "What were the top 3 CPC categories with the highest number of accepted patents in 2018? Return them as a list of CPC categories.", "answer": ["H04", "A61", "G06"]}
{"qid": "easy-0343", "question_type": "4", "question": "What is the title of the patent filed between 2005 and 2008 that took the longest number of days between the filing date and the publication date?", "answer": ["FUEL CARTRIDGE AND FUEL CELL USING THE SAME"]}
{"qid": "easy-0344", "question_type": "4", "question": "What is the title of the patent filed between 2013 and 2015 with the longest number of days elapsed between the filing date and the publication date?", "answer": ["METHOD FOR ELIMINATING RADIOACTIVE IODINE AND HYDROPHILIC RESIN FOR ELIMINATING RADIOACTIVE IODINE"]}
{"qid": "easy-0345", "question_type": "5", "question": "Who were the top 5 authors with the highest number of publications where the titles contain 'Large Language Models' amongst the first 2500 papers at NeurIPS? In the authors column of the database, each entry is a list, not a single string. Return as a list of authors.", "answer": ["Subbarao Kambhampati", "Sarath Sreedharan", "Yuan Cao", "Karthik Valmeekam", "Lintang Sutawika"]}
{"qid": "easy-0346", "question_type": "4", "question": "What is the title of the patent filed between 2013 and 2015 that had the longest publication delay in terms of number of days between the filing date and the publication date?", "answer": ["METHOD FOR ELIMINATING RADIOACTIVE IODINE AND HYDROPHILIC RESIN FOR ELIMINATING RADIOACTIVE IODINE"]}
{"qid": "easy-0347", "question_type": "1", "question": "What was the average time between the filing and issuance of patents from 2007 to 2017? Return an integer representing the number of days by truncating the decimal part.", "answer": 885}
{"qid": "easy-0348", "question_type": "1", "question": "What was the average duration between the filing and issuance of patents from 2006 to 2009? Return an integer representing the number of days by truncating the decimal part.", "answer": 1319}
{"qid": "easy-0349", "question_type": "2", "question": "Which CPC categories were among the top 2 with the highest number of accepted patents in 2014? Return the top categories with the highest approval rates as a list of CPC categories.", "answer": ["H04", "G06"]}
{"qid": "easy-0350", "question_type": "4", "question": "What is the title of the patent filed between 2013 and 2014 that had the longest publication delay in terms of number of days between the filing date and the publication date?", "answer": ["METHOD FOR ELIMINATING RADIOACTIVE IODINE AND HYDROPHILIC RESIN FOR ELIMINATING RADIOACTIVE IODINE"]}
{"qid": "easy-0351", "question_type": "1", "question": "What was the average duration between the filing and issuance of patents from 2013 to 2017? Return an integer representing the number of days by truncating the decimal part.", "answer": 769}
{"qid": "easy-0352", "question_type": "6", "question": "What proportion of NeurIPS papers have fewer than 10 authors? In the authors column of the database, each entry is a list, not a single string. Return a value between 0 and 1.", "answer": 0.9497907949790795}
{"qid": "easy-0353", "question_type": "1", "question": "What was the average duration between the filing and issuance of patents from 2011 to 2011? Return an integer representing the number of days by truncating the decimal part.", "answer": 1054}
{"qid": "easy-0354", "question_type": "6", "question": "What's the ratio of NeurIPS papers that have more than 3 authors? In the authors column of the database, each entry is a list, not a single string. Return a value between 0 and 1.", "answer": 0.702928870292887}
{"qid": "easy-0355", "question_type": "6", "question": "What percentage of NeurIPS papers have exactly 2 authors? In the authors column of the database, each entry is a list, not a single string. Return a value between 0 and 1.", "answer": 0.100697350069735}
{"qid": "easy-0356", "question_type": "1", "question": "What was the average duration between the filing and issuance of patents from 2011 to 2012? Return an integer representing the number of days by truncating the decimal part.", "answer": 1031}
{"qid": "easy-0357", "question_type": "1", "question": "What was the typical time span between the submission and approval of patents from 2011 to 2015? Return an integer representing the number of days by truncating the decimal part.", "answer": 898}
{"qid": "easy-0358", "question_type": "3", "question": "How does the number of patent applications filed in 2013 compare proportionally to those filed in the 2017? Return a number between 0 and 1. Please note that each row represents a unique patent application, and not all patent applications are assigned a patent number.", "answer": 1.0989902632527948}
{"qid": "easy-0359", "question_type": "1", "question": "What was the average duration between the filing and issuance of patents from 2013 to 2013? Return an integer representing the number of days by truncating the decimal part.", "answer": 912}
{"qid": "easy-0360", "question_type": "1", "question": "What was the average time between the filing and issuance of patents from 2012 to 2015? Return an integer representing the number of days by truncating the decimal part.", "answer": 858}
{"qid": "easy-0361", "question_type": "2", "question": "Which IPCR categories were among the top 2 with the highest number of accepted patents in 2004? Return the top categories with the highest approval rates as a list of IPCR categories.", "answer": ["G06", "H04"]}
{"qid": "easy-0362", "question_type": "6", "question": "What percentage of NeurIPS papers have exactly 10 authors? In the authors column of the database, each entry is a list, not a single string. Return a value between 0 and 1.", "answer": 0.015899581589958158}
{"qid": "easy-0363", "question_type": "3", "question": "How does the number of patent applications filed in 2010 compare proportionally to those filed in the 2009? Return a number between 0 and 1. Please note that each row represents a unique patent application, and not all patent applications are assigned a patent number.", "answer": 0.9884238646482636}
{"qid": "easy-0364", "question_type": "3", "question": "How does the number of patent applications filed in 2011 compare proportionally to those filed in the 2010? Return a number between 0 and 1. Please note that each row represents a unique patent application, and not all patent applications are assigned a patent number.", "answer": 6.515315315315315}
{"qid": "easy-0365", "question_type": "4", "question": "What is the title of the patent filed between 2012 and 2012 that took the longest number of days between the filing date and the publication date?", "answer": ["EVALUATING KEYWORD PERFORMANCE"]}
{"qid": "easy-0366", "question_type": "1", "question": "What was the typical time span between the submission and approval of patents from 2008 to 2014? Return an integer representing the number of days by truncating the decimal part.", "answer": 958}
{"qid": "easy-0367", "question_type": "5", "question": "Who were the top 3 authors with the most publications amongst the first 2800 papers at NeurIPS? In the authors column of the database, each entry is a list, not a single string. Return as a list of authors.", "answer": ["Ludwig Schmidt", "Bo Li", "Bo Han"]}
{"qid": "easy-0368", "question_type": "6", "question": "What proportion of NeurIPS papers have exactly 2 authors? In the authors column of the database, each entry is a list, not a single string. Return a value between 0 and 1.", "answer": 0.100697350069735}
{"qid": "easy-0369", "question_type": "4", "question": "What is the title of the patent filed between 2011 and 2016 that took the longest number of days between the filing date and the publication date?", "answer": ["EVALUATING KEYWORD PERFORMANCE"]}
{"qid": "easy-0370", "question_type": "3", "question": "How does the number of patent applications filed in 2006 compare proportionally to those filed in the 2004? Return a number between 0 and 1. Please note that each row represents a unique patent application, and not all patent applications are assigned a patent number.", "answer": 0.2088613125928515}
{"qid": "easy-0371", "question_type": "3", "question": "How does the number of patent applications filed in 2012 compare proportionally to those filed in the 2008? Return a number between 0 and 1. Please note that each row represents a unique patent application, and not all patent applications are assigned a patent number.", "answer": 1.2412060301507537}
{"qid": "easy-0372", "question_type": "4", "question": "What is the title of the patent filed between 2005 and 2014 with the longest number of days elapsed between the filing date and the publication date?", "answer": ["FUEL CARTRIDGE AND FUEL CELL USING THE SAME"]}
{"qid": "easy-0373", "question_type": "1", "question": "What was the average time between the filing and issuance of patents from 2006 to 2006? Return an integer representing the number of days by truncating the decimal part.", "answer": 1348}
{"qid": "easy-0374", "question_type": "2", "question": "Which IPCR categories were among the top 2 with the highest number of accepted patents in 2006? Return the top categories with the highest approval rates as a list of IPCR categories.", "answer": ["G06", "H01"]}
{"qid": "easy-0375", "question_type": "1", "question": "What was the average duration between the filing and issuance of patents from 2009 to 2018? Return an integer representing the number of days by truncating the decimal part.", "answer": 839}
{"qid": "easy-0376", "question_type": "2", "question": "Which CPC categories were among the top 2 with the highest number of accepted patents in 2015? Return the top categories with the highest approval rates as a list of CPC categories.", "answer": ["H04", "H01"]}
{"qid": "easy-0377", "question_type": "6", "question": "What percentage of NeurIPS papers have fewer than or equal to 3 authors? In the authors column of the database, each entry is a list, not a single string. Return a value between 0 and 1.", "answer": 0.29707112970711297}
{"qid": "easy-0378", "question_type": "3", "question": "How does the number of patent applications filed in 2007 compare proportionally to those filed in the 2010? Return a number between 0 and 1. Please note that each row represents a unique patent application, and not all patent applications are assigned a patent number.", "answer": 2.5225225225225225}
{"qid": "easy-0379", "question_type": "5", "question": "Who were the top 5 authors with the most publications where the titles contain 'Large Language Models' amongst the first 1200 papers at NeurIPS? In the authors column of the database, each entry is a list, not a single string. Return as a list of authors.", "answer": ["Yuan Cao", "Lintang Sutawika", "Subbarao Kambhampati", "Karthik Valmeekam", "Sarath Sreedharan"]}
{"qid": "easy-0380", "question_type": "5", "question": "Which 5 authors had the most publications where the titles contain 'Large Language Models' amongst the first 1500 papers at NeurIPS? In the authors column of the database, each entry is a list, not a single string. Return as a list of authors.", "answer": ["Karthik Valmeekam", "Sarath Sreedharan", "Subbarao Kambhampati", "Yuan Cao", "Lintang Sutawika"]}
{"qid": "easy-0381", "question_type": "5", "question": "Who were the top 5 authors with the highest number of publications where the titles contain 'Large Language Models' amongst the first 1200 papers at NeurIPS? In the authors column of the database, each entry is a list, not a single string. Return as a list of authors.", "answer": ["Yuan Cao", "Lintang Sutawika", "Subbarao Kambhampati", "Karthik Valmeekam", "Sarath Sreedharan"]}
{"qid": "easy-0382", "question_type": "3", "question": "How does the number of patent applications filed in 2013 compare proportionally to those filed in the 2008? Return a number between 0 and 1. Please note that each row represents a unique patent application, and not all patent applications are assigned a patent number.", "answer": 6.806253489670575}
{"qid": "easy-0383", "question_type": "4", "question": "What is the title of the patent filed between 2017 and 2017 that had the longest publication delay in terms of number of days between the filing date and the publication date?", "answer": ["NUCLEIC ACID COMPOUNDS FOR BINDING GROWTH DIFFERENTIATION FACTOR 11"]}
{"qid": "easy-0384", "question_type": "2", "question": "What were the top 2 IPCR categories with the highest number of accepted patents in 2007? Return them as a list of IPCR categories.", "answer": ["G06", "H04"]}
{"qid": "easy-0385", "question_type": "2", "question": "What were the top 2 IPCR categories with the highest number of accepted patents in 2009? Return them as a list of IPCR categories.", "answer": ["G06", "H04"]}
{"qid": "easy-0386", "question_type": "3", "question": "How does the number of patent applications filed in 2013 compare proportionally to those filed in the 2014? Return a number between 0 and 1. Please note that each row represents a unique patent application, and not all patent applications are assigned a patent number.", "answer": 1.1907785484028524}
{"qid": "easy-0387", "question_type": "1", "question": "What was the typical time span between the submission and approval of patents from 2005 to 2010? Return an integer representing the number of days by truncating the decimal part.", "answer": 1300}
{"qid": "easy-0388", "question_type": "6", "question": "What proportion of NeurIPS papers have fewer than 5 authors? In the authors column of the database, each entry is a list, not a single string. Return a value between 0 and 1.", "answer": 0.5101813110181311}
{"qid": "easy-0389", "question_type": "6", "question": "What's the ratio of NeurIPS papers that have fewer than or equal to 8 authors? In the authors column of the database, each entry is a list, not a single string. Return a value between 0 and 1.", "answer": 0.9232914923291492}
{"qid": "easy-0390", "question_type": "4", "question": "What is the title of the patent filed between 2014 and 2014 that had the longest publication delay in terms of number of days between the filing date and the publication date?", "answer": ["METHOD FOR ELIMINATING RADIOACTIVE IODINE AND HYDROPHILIC RESIN FOR ELIMINATING RADIOACTIVE IODINE"]}
{"qid": "easy-0391", "question_type": "6", "question": "What percentage of NeurIPS papers have fewer than or equal to 5 authors? In the authors column of the database, each entry is a list, not a single string. Return a value between 0 and 1.", "answer": 0.6728033472803348}
{"qid": "easy-0392", "question_type": "2", "question": "Which IPCR categories were among the top 2 with the highest number of accepted patents in 2009? Return the top categories with the highest approval rates as a list of IPCR categories.", "answer": ["G06", "H04"]}
{"qid": "easy-0393", "question_type": "6", "question": "What percentage of NeurIPS papers have more than 5 authors? In the authors column of the database, each entry is a list, not a single string. Return a value between 0 and 1.", "answer": 0.32719665271966525}
{"qid": "easy-0394", "question_type": "1", "question": "What was the typical time span between the submission and approval of patents from 2009 to 2014? Return an integer representing the number of days by truncating the decimal part.", "answer": 941}
{"qid": "easy-0395", "question_type": "3", "question": "How does the number of patent applications filed in 2006 compare proportionally to those filed in the 2004? Return a number between 0 and 1. Please note that each row represents a unique patent application, and not all patent applications are assigned a patent number.", "answer": 0.2088613125928515}
{"qid": "easy-0396", "question_type": "6", "question": "What's the ratio of NeurIPS papers that have exactly 5 authors? In the authors column of the database, each entry is a list, not a single string. Return a value between 0 and 1.", "answer": 0.16262203626220362}
{"qid": "easy-0397", "question_type": "6", "question": "What's the ratio of NeurIPS papers that have greater than or equal to 3 authors? In the authors column of the database, each entry is a list, not a single string. Return a value between 0 and 1.", "answer": 0.891213389121339}
{"qid": "easy-0398", "question_type": "4", "question": "What is the title of the patent filed between 2010 and 2015 that had the longest publication delay in terms of number of days between the filing date and the publication date?", "answer": ["EVALUATING KEYWORD PERFORMANCE"]}
{"qid": "easy-0399", "question_type": "4", "question": "What is the title of the patent filed between 2017 and 2017 that took the longest number of days between the filing date and the publication date?", "answer": ["NUCLEIC ACID COMPOUNDS FOR BINDING GROWTH DIFFERENTIATION FACTOR 11"]}
{"qid": "easy-0400", "question_type": "1", "question": "What was the average time between the filing and issuance of patents from 2005 to 2015? Return an integer representing the number of days by truncating the decimal part.", "answer": 994}
{"qid": "easy-0401", "question_type": "4", "question": "What is the title of the patent filed between 2015 and 2016 that took the longest number of days between the filing date and the publication date?", "answer": ["BEARING CENTERING SPRING WITH INTEGRAL OUTER RINGS"]}
{"qid": "easy-0402", "question_type": "6", "question": "What proportion of NeurIPS papers have fewer than or equal to 9 authors? In the authors column of the database, each entry is a list, not a single string. Return a value between 0 and 1.", "answer": 0.9497907949790795}
{"qid": "easy-0403", "question_type": "4", "question": "What is the title of the patent filed between 2007 and 2008 that took the longest number of days between the filing date and the publication date?", "answer": ["FUEL CARTRIDGE AND FUEL CELL USING THE SAME"]}
{"qid": "easy-0404", "question_type": "6", "question": "What percentage of NeurIPS papers have fewer than or equal to 9 authors? In the authors column of the database, each entry is a list, not a single string. Return a value between 0 and 1.", "answer": 0.9497907949790795}
{"qid": "easy-0405", "question_type": "2", "question": "Which CPC categories were among the top 2 with the highest number of accepted patents in 2016? Return the top categories with the highest approval rates as a list of CPC categories.", "answer": ["H04", "H01"]}
{"qid": "easy-0406", "question_type": "5", "question": "Who were the top 4 authors with the most publications where the titles contain 'Large Language Models' amongst the first 3500 papers at NeurIPS? In the authors column of the database, each entry is a list, not a single string. Return as a list of authors.", "answer": ["Sarath Sreedharan", "William Yang Wang", "Karthik Valmeekam", "Subbarao Kambhampati"]}
{"qid": "easy-0407", "question_type": "6", "question": "What proportion of NeurIPS papers have greater than or equal to 9 authors? In the authors column of the database, each entry is a list, not a single string. Return a value between 0 and 1.", "answer": 0.07670850767085077}
{"qid": "easy-0408", "question_type": "5", "question": "Who were the top 4 authors with the most publications where the titles contain 'Large Language Models' amongst the first 3500 papers at NeurIPS? In the authors column of the database, each entry is a list, not a single string. Return as a list of authors.", "answer": ["Sarath Sreedharan", "William Yang Wang", "Karthik Valmeekam", "Subbarao Kambhampati"]}
{"qid": "easy-0409", "question_type": "4", "question": "What is the title of the patent filed between 2011 and 2017 that had the longest publication delay in terms of number of days between the filing date and the publication date?", "answer": ["EVALUATING KEYWORD PERFORMANCE"]}
{"qid": "easy-0410", "question_type": "4", "question": "What is the title of the patent filed between 2015 and 2017 with the longest number of days elapsed between the filing date and the publication date?", "answer": ["BEARING CENTERING SPRING WITH INTEGRAL OUTER RINGS"]}
{"qid": "easy-0411", "question_type": "4", "question": "What is the title of the patent filed between 2008 and 2014 with the longest number of days elapsed between the filing date and the publication date?", "answer": ["FUEL CARTRIDGE AND FUEL CELL USING THE SAME"]}
{"qid": "easy-0412", "question_type": "2", "question": "Which CPC categories were among the top 2 with the highest number of accepted patents in 2012? Return the top categories with the highest approval rates as a list of CPC categories.", "answer": ["H04", "G06"]}
{"qid": "easy-0413", "question_type": "2", "question": "What were the top 3 CPC categories with the highest number of accepted patents in 2018? Return them as a list of CPC categories.", "answer": ["H04", "A61", "G06"]}
{"qid": "easy-0414", "question_type": "5", "question": "Who were the top 4 authors with the highest number of publications where the titles contain 'Large Language Models' amongst the first 3200 papers at NeurIPS? In the authors column of the database, each entry is a list, not a single string. Return as a list of authors.", "answer": ["Karthik Valmeekam", "William Yang Wang", "Sarath Sreedharan", "Subbarao Kambhampati"]}
{"qid": "easy-0415", "question_type": "4", "question": "What is the title of the patent filed between 2009 and 2010 with the longest number of days elapsed between the filing date and the publication date?", "answer": ["DYNAMIC TISSUE HOLDING DEVICE WITH LOW PROFILE SPRING"]}
{"qid": "easy-0416", "question_type": "1", "question": "What was the typical time span between the submission and approval of patents from 2017 to 2018? Return an integer representing the number of days by truncating the decimal part.", "answer": 314}
{"qid": "easy-0417", "question_type": "3", "question": "How does the number of patent applications filed in 2014 compare proportionally to those filed in the 2011? Return a number between 0 and 1. Please note that each row represents a unique patent application, and not all patent applications are assigned a patent number.", "answer": 1.4155143805309736}
{"qid": "easy-0418", "question_type": "4", "question": "What is the title of the patent filed between 2016 and 2016 with the longest number of days elapsed between the filing date and the publication date?", "answer": ["System and method for sterilizing and/or deimmunizing an object"]}
{"qid": "easy-0419", "question_type": "4", "question": "What is the title of the patent filed between 2010 and 2011 with the longest number of days elapsed between the filing date and the publication date?", "answer": ["Organic-Inorganic Hybrid Multilayer Gate Dielectrics for Thin-Film Transistors"]}
{"qid": "easy-0420", "question_type": "1", "question": "What was the average time between the filing and issuance of patents from 2006 to 2006? Return an integer representing the number of days by truncating the decimal part.", "answer": 1348}
{"qid": "easy-0421", "question_type": "1", "question": "What was the average time between the filing and issuance of patents from 2018 to 2018? Return an integer representing the number of days by truncating the decimal part.", "answer": 160}
{"qid": "easy-0422", "question_type": "3", "question": "How does the number of patent applications filed in 2009 compare proportionally to those filed in the 2013? Return a number between 0 and 1. Please note that each row represents a unique patent application, and not all patent applications are assigned a patent number.", "answer": 0.09212469237079574}
{"qid": "easy-0423", "question_type": "3", "question": "How does the number of patent applications filed in 2009 compare proportionally to those filed in the 2015? Return a number between 0 and 1. Please note that each row represents a unique patent application, and not all patent applications are assigned a patent number.", "answer": 0.2051516258677384}
{"qid": "easy-0424", "question_type": "6", "question": "What proportion of NeurIPS papers have greater than or equal to 2 authors? In the authors column of the database, each entry is a list, not a single string. Return a value between 0 and 1.", "answer": 0.9919107391910739}
{"qid": "easy-0425", "question_type": "6", "question": "What percentage of NeurIPS papers have exactly 4 authors? In the authors column of the database, each entry is a list, not a single string. Return a value between 0 and 1.", "answer": 0.21311018131101814}
{"qid": "easy-0426", "question_type": "4", "question": "What is the title of the patent filed between 2013 and 2015 with the longest number of days elapsed between the filing date and the publication date?", "answer": ["METHOD FOR ELIMINATING RADIOACTIVE IODINE AND HYDROPHILIC RESIN FOR ELIMINATING RADIOACTIVE IODINE"]}
{"qid": "easy-0427", "question_type": "4", "question": "What is the title of the patent filed between 2016 and 2016 that had the longest publication delay in terms of number of days between the filing date and the publication date?", "answer": ["System and method for sterilizing and/or deimmunizing an object"]}
{"qid": "easy-0428", "question_type": "1", "question": "What was the typical time span between the submission and approval of patents from 2007 to 2011? Return an integer representing the number of days by truncating the decimal part.", "answer": 1159}
{"qid": "easy-0429", "question_type": "1", "question": "What was the average time between the filing and issuance of patents from 2014 to 2018? Return an integer representing the number of days by truncating the decimal part.", "answer": 683}
{"qid": "easy-0430", "question_type": "1", "question": "What was the typical time span between the submission and approval of patents from 2006 to 2008? Return an integer representing the number of days by truncating the decimal part.", "answer": 1340}
{"qid": "easy-0431", "question_type": "4", "question": "What is the title of the patent filed between 2005 and 2013 with the longest number of days elapsed between the filing date and the publication date?", "answer": ["FUEL CARTRIDGE AND FUEL CELL USING THE SAME"]}
{"qid": "easy-0432", "question_type": "4", "question": "What is the title of the patent filed between 2009 and 2009 with the longest number of days elapsed between the filing date and the publication date?", "answer": ["DYNAMIC TISSUE HOLDING DEVICE WITH LOW PROFILE SPRING"]}
{"qid": "easy-0433", "question_type": "4", "question": "What is the title of the patent filed between 2008 and 2011 that took the longest number of days between the filing date and the publication date?", "answer": ["FUEL CARTRIDGE AND FUEL CELL USING THE SAME"]}
{"qid": "easy-0434", "question_type": "6", "question": "What percentage of NeurIPS papers have fewer than 4 authors? In the authors column of the database, each entry is a list, not a single string. Return a value between 0 and 1.", "answer": 0.29707112970711297}
{"qid": "easy-0435", "question_type": "4", "question": "What is the title of the patent filed between 2011 and 2011 that had the longest publication delay in terms of number of days between the filing date and the publication date?", "answer": ["Organic-Inorganic Hybrid Multilayer Gate Dielectrics for Thin-Film Transistors"]}
{"qid": "easy-0436", "question_type": "1", "question": "What was the average duration between the filing and issuance of patents from 2009 to 2013? Return an integer representing the number of days by truncating the decimal part.", "answer": 983}
{"qid": "easy-0437", "question_type": "1", "question": "What was the average time between the filing and issuance of patents from 2017 to 2017? Return an integer representing the number of days by truncating the decimal part.", "answer": 343}
{"qid": "easy-0438", "question_type": "1", "question": "What was the typical time span between the submission and approval of patents from 2005 to 2010? Return an integer representing the number of days by truncating the decimal part.", "answer": 1300}
{"qid": "easy-0439", "question_type": "6", "question": "What's the ratio of NeurIPS papers that have fewer than or equal to 10 authors? In the authors column of the database, each entry is a list, not a single string. Return a value between 0 and 1.", "answer": 0.9656903765690377}
{"qid": "easy-0440", "question_type": "2", "question": "Which IPCR categories were among the top 2 with the highest number of accepted patents in 2016? Return the top categories with the highest approval rates as a list of IPCR categories.", "answer": ["H04", "H01"]}
{"qid": "easy-0441", "question_type": "4", "question": "What is the title of the patent filed between 2006 and 2016 with the longest number of days elapsed between the filing date and the publication date?", "answer": ["FUEL CARTRIDGE AND FUEL CELL USING THE SAME"]}
{"qid": "easy-0442", "question_type": "6", "question": "What proportion of NeurIPS papers have fewer than 3 authors? In the authors column of the database, each entry is a list, not a single string. Return a value between 0 and 1.", "answer": 0.1087866108786611}
{"qid": "easy-0443", "question_type": "3", "question": "How does the number of patent applications filed in 2013 compare proportionally to those filed in the 2008? Return a number between 0 and 1. Please note that each row represents a unique patent application, and not all patent applications are assigned a patent number.", "answer": 6.806253489670575}
{"qid": "easy-0444", "question_type": "1", "question": "What was the average time between the filing and issuance of patents from 2013 to 2016? Return an integer representing the number of days by truncating the decimal part.", "answer": 790}
{"qid": "easy-0445", "question_type": "1", "question": "What was the average duration between the filing and issuance of patents from 2011 to 2011? Return an integer representing the number of days by truncating the decimal part.", "answer": 1054}
{"qid": "easy-0446", "question_type": "3", "question": "How does the number of patent applications filed in 2014 compare proportionally to those filed in the 2009? Return a number between 0 and 1. Please note that each row represents a unique patent application, and not all patent applications are assigned a patent number.", "answer": 9.115761353517364}
{"qid": "easy-0447", "question_type": "2", "question": "Which IPCR categories were among the top 2 with the highest number of accepted patents in 2009? Return the top categories with the highest approval rates as a list of IPCR categories.", "answer": ["G06", "H04"]}
{"qid": "easy-0448", "question_type": "3", "question": "How does the number of patent applications filed in 2008 compare proportionally to those filed in the 2006? Return a number between 0 and 1. Please note that each row represents a unique patent application, and not all patent applications are assigned a patent number.", "answer": 0.7493723849372385}
{"qid": "easy-0449", "question_type": "6", "question": "What proportion of NeurIPS papers have fewer than or equal to 9 authors? In the authors column of the database, each entry is a list, not a single string. Return a value between 0 and 1.", "answer": 0.9497907949790795}
{"qid": "easy-0450", "question_type": "4", "question": "What is the title of the patent filed between 2007 and 2011 that had the longest publication delay in terms of number of days between the filing date and the publication date?", "answer": ["FUEL CARTRIDGE AND FUEL CELL USING THE SAME"]}
{"qid": "easy-0451", "question_type": "3", "question": "How does the number of patent applications filed in 2009 compare proportionally to those filed in the 2014? Return a number between 0 and 1. Please note that each row represents a unique patent application, and not all patent applications are assigned a patent number.", "answer": 0.10970010745335547}
{"qid": "easy-0452", "question_type": "2", "question": "What were the top 2 CPC categories with the highest number of accepted patents in 2016? Return them as a list of CPC categories.", "answer": ["H04", "H01"]}
{"qid": "easy-0453", "question_type": "2", "question": "What were the top 2 IPCR categories with the highest number of accepted patents in 2015? Return them as a list of IPCR categories.", "answer": ["H04", "H01"]}
{"qid": "easy-0454", "question_type": "4", "question": "What is the title of the patent filed between 2005 and 2010 that took the longest number of days between the filing date and the publication date?", "answer": ["FUEL CARTRIDGE AND FUEL CELL USING THE SAME"]}
{"qid": "easy-0455", "question_type": "2", "question": "What were the top 3 CPC categories with the highest number of accepted patents in 2018? Return them as a list of CPC categories.", "answer": ["H04", "A61", "G06"]}
{"qid": "easy-0456", "question_type": "6", "question": "What's the ratio of NeurIPS papers that have fewer than 7 authors? In the authors column of the database, each entry is a list, not a single string. Return a value between 0 and 1.", "answer": 0.7927475592747559}
{"qid": "easy-0457", "question_type": "1", "question": "What was the average duration between the filing and issuance of patents from 2016 to 2018? Return an integer representing the number of days by truncating the decimal part.", "answer": 487}
{"qid": "easy-0458", "question_type": "5", "question": "Which 3 authors had the most publications where the titles contain 'Large Language Models' amongst the first 2600 papers at NeurIPS? In the authors column of the database, each entry is a list, not a single string. Return as a list of authors.", "answer": ["Karthik Valmeekam", "Sarath Sreedharan", "Subbarao Kambhampati"]}
{"qid": "easy-0459", "question_type": "3", "question": "How does the number of patent applications filed in 2016 compare proportionally to those filed in the 2007? Return a number between 0 and 1. Please note that each row represents a unique patent application, and not all patent applications are assigned a patent number.", "answer": 4.818214285714285}
{"qid": "easy-0460", "question_type": "2", "question": "Which IPCR categories were among the top 2 with the highest number of accepted patents in 2008? Return the top categories with the highest approval rates as a list of IPCR categories.", "answer": ["G06", "H04"]}
{"qid": "easy-0461", "question_type": "1", "question": "What was the typical time span between the submission and approval of patents from 2009 to 2014? Return an integer representing the number of days by truncating the decimal part.", "answer": 941}
{"qid": "easy-0462", "question_type": "3", "question": "How does the number of patent applications filed in 2013 compare proportionally to those filed in the 2006? Return a number between 0 and 1. Please note that each row represents a unique patent application, and not all patent applications are assigned a patent number.", "answer": 5.100418410041841}
{"qid": "easy-0463", "question_type": "6", "question": "What percentage of NeurIPS papers have fewer than or equal to 10 authors? In the authors column of the database, each entry is a list, not a single string. Return a value between 0 and 1.", "answer": 0.9656903765690377}
{"qid": "easy-0464", "question_type": "3", "question": "How does the number of patent applications filed in 2013 compare proportionally to those filed in the 2017? Return a number between 0 and 1. Please note that each row represents a unique patent application, and not all patent applications are assigned a patent number.", "answer": 1.0989902632527948}
{"qid": "easy-0465", "question_type": "2", "question": "Which CPC categories were among the top 2 with the highest number of accepted patents in 2017? Return the top categories with the highest approval rates as a list of CPC categories.", "answer": ["H01", "H04"]}
{"qid": "easy-0466", "question_type": "3", "question": "How does the number of patent applications filed in 2017 compare proportionally to those filed in the 2012? Return a number between 0 and 1. Please note that each row represents a unique patent application, and not all patent applications are assigned a patent number.", "answer": 4.989653621232568}
{"qid": "easy-0467", "question_type": "1", "question": "What was the typical time span between the submission and approval of patents from 2007 to 2009? Return an integer representing the number of days by truncating the decimal part.", "answer": 1307}
{"qid": "easy-0468", "question_type": "3", "question": "How does the number of patent applications filed in 2012 compare proportionally to those filed in the 2010? Return a number between 0 and 1. Please note that each row represents a unique patent application, and not all patent applications are assigned a patent number.", "answer": 2.002702702702703}
{"qid": "easy-0469", "question_type": "1", "question": "What was the average time between the filing and issuance of patents from 2004 to 2004? Return an integer representing the number of days by truncating the decimal part.", "answer": 1314}
{"qid": "easy-0470", "question_type": "3", "question": "How does the number of patent applications filed in 2010 compare proportionally to those filed in the 2012? Return a number between 0 and 1. Please note that each row represents a unique patent application, and not all patent applications are assigned a patent number.", "answer": 0.4993252361673414}
{"qid": "easy-0471", "question_type": "5", "question": "Who were the top 4 authors with the most publications where the titles contain 'Large Language Models' amongst the first 3100 papers at NeurIPS? In the authors column of the database, each entry is a list, not a single string. Return as a list of authors.", "answer": ["Subbarao Kambhampati", "William Yang Wang", "Karthik Valmeekam", "Sarath Sreedharan"]}
{"qid": "easy-0472", "question_type": "6", "question": "What percentage of NeurIPS papers have more than 10 authors? In the authors column of the database, each entry is a list, not a single string. Return a value between 0 and 1.", "answer": 0.03430962343096234}
{"qid": "easy-0473", "question_type": "6", "question": "What proportion of NeurIPS papers have exactly 5 authors? In the authors column of the database, each entry is a list, not a single string. Return a value between 0 and 1.", "answer": 0.16262203626220362}
{"qid": "easy-0474", "question_type": "1", "question": "What was the typical time span between the submission and approval of patents from 2010 to 2015? Return an integer representing the number of days by truncating the decimal part.", "answer": 905}
{"qid": "easy-0475", "question_type": "2", "question": "What were the top 2 IPCR categories with the highest number of accepted patents in 2014? Return them as a list of IPCR categories.", "answer": ["H04", "G06"]}
{"qid": "easy-0476", "question_type": "1", "question": "What was the average duration between the filing and issuance of patents from 2009 to 2014? Return an integer representing the number of days by truncating the decimal part.", "answer": 941}
{"qid": "easy-0477", "question_type": "6", "question": "What percentage of NeurIPS papers have greater than or equal to 7 authors? In the authors column of the database, each entry is a list, not a single string. Return a value between 0 and 1.", "answer": 0.20725244072524407}
{"qid": "easy-0478", "question_type": "1", "question": "What was the typical time span between the submission and approval of patents from 2018 to 2018? Return an integer representing the number of days by truncating the decimal part.", "answer": 160}
{"qid": "easy-0479", "question_type": "3", "question": "How does the number of patent applications filed in 2017 compare proportionally to those filed in the 2018? Return a number between 0 and 1. Please note that each row represents a unique patent application, and not all patent applications are assigned a patent number.", "answer": 0.34739578439663005}
{"qid": "easy-0480", "question_type": "3", "question": "How does the number of patent applications filed in 2009 compare proportionally to those filed in the 2015? Return a number between 0 and 1. Please note that each row represents a unique patent application, and not all patent applications are assigned a patent number.", "answer": 0.2051516258677384}
{"qid": "easy-0481", "question_type": "3", "question": "How does the number of patent applications filed in 2007 compare proportionally to those filed in the 2012? Return a number between 0 and 1. Please note that each row represents a unique patent application, and not all patent applications are assigned a patent number.", "answer": 1.2595591542959963}
{"qid": "easy-0482", "question_type": "3", "question": "How does the number of patent applications filed in 2017 compare proportionally to those filed in the 2015? Return a number between 0 and 1. Please note that each row represents a unique patent application, and not all patent applications are assigned a patent number.", "answer": 2.0263061746437705}
{"qid": "easy-0483", "question_type": "5", "question": "Who were the top 5 authors with the most publications where the titles contain 'Large Language Models' amongst the first 1400 papers at NeurIPS? In the authors column of the database, each entry is a list, not a single string. Return as a list of authors.", "answer": ["Yuan Cao", "Sarath Sreedharan", "Subbarao Kambhampati", "Lintang Sutawika", "Karthik Valmeekam"]}
{"qid": "easy-0484", "question_type": "1", "question": "What was the average duration between the filing and issuance of patents from 2015 to 2018? Return an integer representing the number of days by truncating the decimal part.", "answer": 565}
{"qid": "easy-0485", "question_type": "6", "question": "What's the ratio of NeurIPS papers that have exactly 10 authors? In the authors column of the database, each entry is a list, not a single string. Return a value between 0 and 1.", "answer": 0.015899581589958158}
{"qid": "easy-0486", "question_type": "2", "question": "Which IPCR categories were among the top 2 with the highest number of accepted patents in 2016? Return the top categories with the highest approval rates as a list of IPCR categories.", "answer": ["H04", "H01"]}
{"qid": "easy-0487", "question_type": "1", "question": "What was the typical time span between the submission and approval of patents from 2013 to 2018? Return an integer representing the number of days by truncating the decimal part.", "answer": 764}
{"qid": "easy-0488", "question_type": "6", "question": "What's the ratio of NeurIPS papers that have fewer than or equal to 2 authors? In the authors column of the database, each entry is a list, not a single string. Return a value between 0 and 1.", "answer": 0.1087866108786611}
{"qid": "easy-0489", "question_type": "2", "question": "Which IPCR categories were among the top 2 with the highest number of accepted patents in 2007? Return the top categories with the highest approval rates as a list of IPCR categories.", "answer": ["G06", "H04"]}
{"qid": "easy-0490", "question_type": "5", "question": "Who were the top 3 authors with the most publications where the titles contain 'Large Language Models' amongst the first 2700 papers at NeurIPS? In the authors column of the database, each entry is a list, not a single string. Return as a list of authors.", "answer": ["Subbarao Kambhampati", "Sarath Sreedharan", "Karthik Valmeekam"]}
{"qid": "easy-0491", "question_type": "3", "question": "How does the number of patent applications filed in 2005 compare proportionally to those filed in the 2012? Return a number between 0 and 1. Please note that each row represents a unique patent application, and not all patent applications are assigned a patent number.", "answer": 1.2798020692757535}
{"qid": "easy-0492", "question_type": "3", "question": "How does the number of patent applications filed in 2014 compare proportionally to those filed in the 2004? Return a number between 0 and 1. Please note that each row represents a unique patent application, and not all patent applications are assigned a patent number.", "answer": 0.8946080573276238}
{"qid": "easy-0493", "question_type": "3", "question": "How does the number of patent applications filed in 2008 compare proportionally to those filed in the 2017? Return a number between 0 and 1. Please note that each row represents a unique patent application, and not all patent applications are assigned a patent number.", "answer": 0.16146772448611613}
{"qid": "easy-0494", "question_type": "6", "question": "What percentage of NeurIPS papers have fewer than 8 authors? In the authors column of the database, each entry is a list, not a single string. Return a value between 0 and 1.", "answer": 0.8716875871687587}
{"qid": "easy-0495", "question_type": "6", "question": "What proportion of NeurIPS papers have fewer than 9 authors? In the authors column of the database, each entry is a list, not a single string. Return a value between 0 and 1.", "answer": 0.9232914923291492}
{"qid": "easy-0496", "question_type": "1", "question": "What was the typical time span between the submission and approval of patents from 2010 to 2012? Return an integer representing the number of days by truncating the decimal part.", "answer": 1042}
{"qid": "easy-0497", "question_type": "1", "question": "What was the average time between the filing and issuance of patents from 2018 to 2018? Return an integer representing the number of days by truncating the decimal part.", "answer": 160}
{"qid": "easy-0498", "question_type": "2", "question": "Which CPC categories were among the top 2 with the highest number of accepted patents in 2013? Return the top categories with the highest approval rates as a list of CPC categories.", "answer": ["H04", "G06"]}
{"qid": "easy-0499", "question_type": "2", "question": "Which IPCR categories were among the top 2 with the highest number of accepted patents in 2013? Return the top categories with the highest approval rates as a list of IPCR categories.", "answer": ["H04", "G06"]}
{"qid": "easy-0500", "question_type": "1", "question": "What was the average duration between the filing and issuance of patents from 2006 to 2008? Return an integer representing the number of days by truncating the decimal part.", "answer": 1340}
{"qid": "easy-0501", "question_type": "5", "question": "Who were the top 5 authors with the highest number of publications where the titles contain 'Large Language Models' amongst the first 2300 papers at NeurIPS? In the authors column of the database, each entry is a list, not a single string. Return as a list of authors.", "answer": ["Yuan Cao", "Karthik Valmeekam", "Sarath Sreedharan", "Subbarao Kambhampati", "Lintang Sutawika"]}
{"qid": "easy-0502", "question_type": "2", "question": "Which IPCR categories were among the top 2 with the highest number of accepted patents in 2009? Return the top categories with the highest approval rates as a list of IPCR categories.", "answer": ["G06", "H04"]}
{"qid": "easy-0503", "question_type": "6", "question": "What proportion of NeurIPS papers have greater than or equal to 2 authors? In the authors column of the database, each entry is a list, not a single string. Return a value between 0 and 1.", "answer": 0.9919107391910739}
{"qid": "easy-0504", "question_type": "1", "question": "What was the average duration between the filing and issuance of patents from 2013 to 2018? Return an integer representing the number of days by truncating the decimal part.", "answer": 764}
{"qid": "easy-0505", "question_type": "2", "question": "What were the top 2 IPCR categories with the highest number of accepted patents in 2012? Return them as a list of IPCR categories.", "answer": ["G06", "H04"]}
{"qid": "easy-0506", "question_type": "6", "question": "What proportion of NeurIPS papers have fewer than or equal to 7 authors? In the authors column of the database, each entry is a list, not a single string. Return a value between 0 and 1.", "answer": 0.8716875871687587}
{"qid": "easy-0507", "question_type": "6", "question": "What proportion of NeurIPS papers have more than 9 authors? In the authors column of the database, each entry is a list, not a single string. Return a value between 0 and 1.", "answer": 0.0502092050209205}
{"qid": "easy-0508", "question_type": "5", "question": "Which 4 authors had the most publications where the titles contain 'Large Language Models' amongst the first 2900 papers at NeurIPS? In the authors column of the database, each entry is a list, not a single string. Return as a list of authors.", "answer": ["Sarath Sreedharan", "Karthik Valmeekam", "William Yang Wang", "Subbarao Kambhampati"]}
{"qid": "easy-0509", "question_type": "2", "question": "What were the top 2 CPC categories with the highest number of accepted patents in 2015? Return them as a list of CPC categories.", "answer": ["H04", "H01"]}
{"qid": "easy-0510", "question_type": "6", "question": "What percentage of NeurIPS papers have exactly 2 authors? In the authors column of the database, each entry is a list, not a single string. Return a value between 0 and 1.", "answer": 0.100697350069735}
{"qid": "easy-0511", "question_type": "2", "question": "Which IPCR categories were among the top 2 with the highest number of accepted patents in 2010? Return the top categories with the highest approval rates as a list of IPCR categories.", "answer": ["G06", "H04"]}
{"qid": "easy-0512", "question_type": "6", "question": "What's the ratio of NeurIPS papers that have exactly 8 authors? In the authors column of the database, each entry is a list, not a single string. Return a value between 0 and 1.", "answer": 0.05160390516039052}
{"qid": "easy-0513", "question_type": "6", "question": "What proportion of NeurIPS papers have fewer than 4 authors? In the authors column of the database, each entry is a list, not a single string. Return a value between 0 and 1.", "answer": 0.29707112970711297}
{"qid": "easy-0514", "question_type": "2", "question": "What were the top 2 IPCR categories with the highest number of accepted patents in 2017? Return them as a list of IPCR categories.", "answer": ["H01", "H04"]}
{"qid": "easy-0515", "question_type": "1", "question": "What was the average duration between the filing and issuance of patents from 2018 to 2018? Return an integer representing the number of days by truncating the decimal part.", "answer": 160}
{"qid": "easy-0516", "question_type": "5", "question": "Who were the top 4 authors with the highest number of publications where the titles contain 'Large Language Models' at NeurIPS? In the authors column of the database, each entry is a list, not a single string. Return as a list of authors.", "answer": ["Subbarao Kambhampati", "Karthik Valmeekam", "William Yang Wang", "Sarath Sreedharan"]}
{"qid": "easy-0517", "question_type": "6", "question": "What's the ratio of NeurIPS papers that have exactly 5 authors? In the authors column of the database, each entry is a list, not a single string. Return a value between 0 and 1.", "answer": 0.16262203626220362}
{"qid": "easy-0518", "question_type": "1", "question": "What was the average time between the filing and issuance of patents from 2007 to 2014? Return an integer representing the number of days by truncating the decimal part.", "answer": 986}
{"qid": "easy-0519", "question_type": "6", "question": "What percentage of NeurIPS papers have fewer than or equal to 6 authors? In the authors column of the database, each entry is a list, not a single string. Return a value between 0 and 1.", "answer": 0.7927475592747559}
{"qid": "easy-0520", "question_type": "1", "question": "What was the average time between the filing and issuance of patents from 2004 to 2010? Return an integer representing the number of days by truncating the decimal part.", "answer": 1307}
{"qid": "easy-0521", "question_type": "5", "question": "Who were the top 2 authors with the highest number of publications amongst the first 3500 papers at NeurIPS? In the authors column of the database, each entry is a list, not a single string. Return as a list of authors.", "answer": ["Bo Li", "Ludwig Schmidt"]}
{"qid": "easy-0522", "question_type": "5", "question": "Who were the top 5 authors with the highest number of publications where the titles contain 'Large Language Models' amongst the first 1900 papers at NeurIPS? In the authors column of the database, each entry is a list, not a single string. Return as a list of authors.", "answer": ["Sarath Sreedharan", "Karthik Valmeekam", "Yuan Cao", "Lintang Sutawika", "Subbarao Kambhampati"]}
{"qid": "easy-0523", "question_type": "1", "question": "What was the average time between the filing and issuance of patents from 2008 to 2013? Return an integer representing the number of days by truncating the decimal part.", "answer": 1004}
{"qid": "easy-0524", "question_type": "5", "question": "Which 5 authors had the most publications where the titles contain 'Large Language Models' amongst the first 1700 papers at NeurIPS? In the authors column of the database, each entry is a list, not a single string. Return as a list of authors.", "answer": ["Lintang Sutawika", "Subbarao Kambhampati", "Yuan Cao", "Karthik Valmeekam", "Sarath Sreedharan"]}
{"qid": "easy-0525", "question_type": "6", "question": "What proportion of NeurIPS papers have fewer than or equal to 9 authors? In the authors column of the database, each entry is a list, not a single string. Return a value between 0 and 1.", "answer": 0.9497907949790795}
{"qid": "easy-0526", "question_type": "5", "question": "Which 5 authors had the most publications where the titles contain 'Large Language Models' amongst the first 1200 papers at NeurIPS? In the authors column of the database, each entry is a list, not a single string. Return as a list of authors.", "answer": ["Yuan Cao", "Lintang Sutawika", "Subbarao Kambhampati", "Karthik Valmeekam", "Sarath Sreedharan"]}
{"qid": "easy-0527", "question_type": "2", "question": "Which IPCR categories were among the top 2 with the highest number of accepted patents in 2004? Return the top categories with the highest approval rates as a list of IPCR categories.", "answer": ["G06", "H04"]}
{"qid": "easy-0528", "question_type": "5", "question": "Who were the top 5 authors with the most publications where the titles contain 'Large Language Models' amongst the first 1000 papers at NeurIPS? In the authors column of the database, each entry is a list, not a single string. Return as a list of authors.", "answer": ["Yuan Cao", "Lintang Sutawika", "Karthik Valmeekam", "Sarath Sreedharan", "Subbarao Kambhampati"]}
{"qid": "easy-0529", "question_type": "2", "question": "Which IPCR categories were among the top 2 with the highest number of accepted patents in 2005? Return the top categories with the highest approval rates as a list of IPCR categories.", "answer": ["G06", "H04"]}
{"qid": "easy-0530", "question_type": "2", "question": "What were the top 2 IPCR categories with the highest number of accepted patents in 2006? Return them as a list of IPCR categories.", "answer": ["G06", "H01"]}
{"qid": "easy-0531", "question_type": "2", "question": "Which IPCR categories were among the top 2 with the highest number of accepted patents in 2016? Return the top categories with the highest approval rates as a list of IPCR categories.", "answer": ["H04", "H01"]}
{"qid": "easy-0532", "question_type": "5", "question": "Which 4 authors had the most publications where the titles contain 'Large Language Models' amongst the first 3100 papers at NeurIPS? In the authors column of the database, each entry is a list, not a single string. Return as a list of authors.", "answer": ["Subbarao Kambhampati", "William Yang Wang", "Karthik Valmeekam", "Sarath Sreedharan"]}
{"qid": "easy-0533", "question_type": "5", "question": "Which 5 authors had the most publications where the titles contain 'Large Language Models' amongst the first 1800 papers at NeurIPS? In the authors column of the database, each entry is a list, not a single string. Return as a list of authors.", "answer": ["Karthik Valmeekam", "Lintang Sutawika", "Yuan Cao", "Sarath Sreedharan", "Subbarao Kambhampati"]}
{"qid": "easy-0534", "question_type": "2", "question": "What were the top 2 IPCR categories with the highest number of accepted patents in 2017? Return them as a list of IPCR categories.", "answer": ["H01", "H04"]}
{"qid": "easy-0535", "question_type": "2", "question": "What were the top 2 IPCR categories with the highest number of accepted patents in 2014? Return them as a list of IPCR categories.", "answer": ["H04", "G06"]}
{"qid": "easy-0536", "question_type": "5", "question": "Which 4 authors had the most publications where the titles contain 'Large Language Models' at NeurIPS? In the authors column of the database, each entry is a list, not a single string. Return as a list of authors.", "answer": ["Subbarao Kambhampati", "Karthik Valmeekam", "William Yang Wang", "Sarath Sreedharan"]}
{"qid": "easy-0537", "question_type": "2", "question": "What were the top 2 IPCR categories with the highest number of accepted patents in 2011? Return them as a list of IPCR categories.", "answer": ["G06", "H04"]}
{"qid": "easy-0538", "question_type": "2", "question": "What were the top 2 IPCR categories with the highest number of accepted patents in 2008? Return them as a list of IPCR categories.", "answer": ["G06", "H04"]}
{"qid": "easy-0539", "question_type": "2", "question": "What were the top 2 CPC categories with the highest number of accepted patents in 2017? Return them as a list of CPC categories.", "answer": ["H01", "H04"]}
{"qid": "easy-0540", "question_type": "2", "question": "Which CPC categories were among the top 2 with the highest number of accepted patents in 2012? Return the top categories with the highest approval rates as a list of CPC categories.", "answer": ["H04", "G06"]}
{"qid": "easy-0541", "question_type": "5", "question": "Who were the top 4 authors with the most publications where the titles contain 'Large Language Models' at NeurIPS? In the authors column of the database, each entry is a list, not a single string. Return as a list of authors.", "answer": ["Subbarao Kambhampati", "Karthik Valmeekam", "William Yang Wang", "Sarath Sreedharan"]}
{"qid": "easy-0542", "question_type": "5", "question": "Who were the top 5 authors with the most publications where the titles contain 'Large Language Models' amongst the first 1600 papers at NeurIPS? In the authors column of the database, each entry is a list, not a single string. Return as a list of authors.", "answer": ["Karthik Valmeekam", "Sarath Sreedharan", "Subbarao Kambhampati", "Yuan Cao", "Lintang Sutawika"]}
{"qid": "easy-0543", "question_type": "5", "question": "Who were the top 5 authors with the most publications where the titles contain 'Large Language Models' amongst the first 1300 papers at NeurIPS? In the authors column of the database, each entry is a list, not a single string. Return as a list of authors.", "answer": ["Yuan Cao", "Lintang Sutawika", "Subbarao Kambhampati", "Sarath Sreedharan", "Karthik Valmeekam"]}
{"qid": "easy-0544", "question_type": "5", "question": "Who were the top 4 authors with the most publications where the titles contain 'Large Language Models' at NeurIPS? In the authors column of the database, each entry is a list, not a single string. Return as a list of authors.", "answer": ["Subbarao Kambhampati", "Karthik Valmeekam", "William Yang Wang", "Sarath Sreedharan"]}
{"qid": "easy-0545", "question_type": "5", "question": "Who were the top 5 authors with the most publications where the titles contain 'Large Language Models' amongst the first 2100 papers at NeurIPS? In the authors column of the database, each entry is a list, not a single string. Return as a list of authors.", "answer": ["Sarath Sreedharan", "Karthik Valmeekam", "Lintang Sutawika", "Yuan Cao", "Subbarao Kambhampati"]}
{"qid": "easy-0546", "question_type": "5", "question": "Which 5 authors had the most publications where the titles contain 'Large Language Models' amongst the first 1000 papers at NeurIPS? In the authors column of the database, each entry is a list, not a single string. Return as a list of authors.", "answer": ["Yuan Cao", "Lintang Sutawika", "Karthik Valmeekam", "Sarath Sreedharan", "Subbarao Kambhampati"]}
{"qid": "easy-0547", "question_type": "5", "question": "Who were the top 4 authors with the most publications where the titles contain 'Large Language Models' at NeurIPS? In the authors column of the database, each entry is a list, not a single string. Return as a list of authors.", "answer": ["Subbarao Kambhampati", "Karthik Valmeekam", "William Yang Wang", "Sarath Sreedharan"]}
{"qid": "easy-0548", "question_type": "2", "question": "What were the top 3 CPC categories with the highest number of accepted patents in 2011? Return them as a list of CPC categories.", "answer": ["H01", "G01", "H04"]}
{"qid": "easy-0549", "question_type": "2", "question": "Which IPCR categories were among the top 2 with the highest number of accepted patents in 2008? Return the top categories with the highest approval rates as a list of IPCR categories.", "answer": ["G06", "H04"]}
{"qid": "easy-0550", "question_type": "2", "question": "What were the top 2 IPCR categories with the highest number of accepted patents in 2007? Return them as a list of IPCR categories.", "answer": ["G06", "H04"]}
{"qid": "easy-0551", "question_type": "5", "question": "Who were the top 5 authors with the highest number of publications where the titles contain 'Large Language Models' amongst the first 1500 papers at NeurIPS? In the authors column of the database, each entry is a list, not a single string. Return as a list of authors.", "answer": ["Karthik Valmeekam", "Sarath Sreedharan", "Subbarao Kambhampati", "Yuan Cao", "Lintang Sutawika"]}
{"qid": "easy-0552", "question_type": "5", "question": "Which 2 authors had the most publications amongst the first 1400 papers at NeurIPS? In the authors column of the database, each entry is a list, not a single string. Return as a list of authors.", "answer": ["Bernhard Schölkopf", "Mihaela van der Schaar"]}
{"qid": "easy-0553", "question_type": "2", "question": "Which CPC categories were among the top 3 with the highest number of accepted patents in 2018? Return the top categories with the highest approval rates as a list of CPC categories.", "answer": ["H04", "A61", "G06"]}
{"qid": "easy-0554", "question_type": "2", "question": "Which CPC categories were among the top 3 with the highest number of accepted patents in 2011? Return the top categories with the highest approval rates as a list of CPC categories.", "answer": ["H01", "G01", "H04"]}
{"qid": "easy-0555", "question_type": "5", "question": "Who were the top 5 authors with the most publications where the titles contain 'Large Language Models' amongst the first 2400 papers at NeurIPS? In the authors column of the database, each entry is a list, not a single string. Return as a list of authors.", "answer": ["Yuan Cao", "Karthik Valmeekam", "Sarath Sreedharan", "Subbarao Kambhampati", "Lintang Sutawika"]}
{"qid": "easy-0556", "question_type": "5", "question": "Which 5 authors had the most publications where the titles contain 'Large Language Models' amongst the first 1800 papers at NeurIPS? In the authors column of the database, each entry is a list, not a single string. Return as a list of authors.", "answer": ["Karthik Valmeekam", "Lintang Sutawika", "Yuan Cao", "Sarath Sreedharan", "Subbarao Kambhampati"]}
{"qid": "easy-0557", "question_type": "5", "question": "Who were the top 5 authors with the most publications where the titles contain 'Large Language Models' amongst the first 2300 papers at NeurIPS? In the authors column of the database, each entry is a list, not a single string. Return as a list of authors.", "answer": ["Yuan Cao", "Karthik Valmeekam", "Sarath Sreedharan", "Subbarao Kambhampati", "Lintang Sutawika"]}
{"qid": "easy-0558", "question_type": "2", "question": "What were the top 2 IPCR categories with the highest number of accepted patents in 2013? Return them as a list of IPCR categories.", "answer": ["H04", "G06"]}
{"qid": "easy-0559", "question_type": "2", "question": "What were the top 2 CPC categories with the highest number of accepted patents in 2012? Return them as a list of CPC categories.", "answer": ["H04", "G06"]}
{"qid": "easy-0560", "question_type": "5", "question": "Which 5 authors had the most publications where the titles contain 'Large Language Models' amongst the first 2100 papers at NeurIPS? In the authors column of the database, each entry is a list, not a single string. Return as a list of authors.", "answer": ["Sarath Sreedharan", "Karthik Valmeekam", "Lintang Sutawika", "Yuan Cao", "Subbarao Kambhampati"]}
{"qid": "easy-0561", "question_type": "2", "question": "What were the top 2 IPCR categories with the highest number of accepted patents in 2004? Return them as a list of IPCR categories.", "answer": ["G06", "H04"]}
{"qid": "easy-0562", "question_type": "2", "question": "What were the top 2 IPCR categories with the highest number of accepted patents in 2008? Return them as a list of IPCR categories.", "answer": ["G06", "H04"]}
{"qid": "easy-0563", "question_type": "5", "question": "Who were the top 5 authors with the highest number of publications where the titles contain 'Large Language Models' amongst the first 2100 papers at NeurIPS? In the authors column of the database, each entry is a list, not a single string. Return as a list of authors.", "answer": ["Sarath Sreedharan", "Karthik Valmeekam", "Lintang Sutawika", "Yuan Cao", "Subbarao Kambhampati"]}
{"qid": "easy-0564", "question_type": "5", "question": "Which 4 authors had the most publications where the titles contain 'Large Language Models' amongst the first 3500 papers at NeurIPS? In the authors column of the database, each entry is a list, not a single string. Return as a list of authors.", "answer": ["Sarath Sreedharan", "William Yang Wang", "Karthik Valmeekam", "Subbarao Kambhampati"]}
{"qid": "easy-0565", "question_type": "5", "question": "Which 3 authors had the most publications where the titles contain 'Large Language Models' amongst the first 2600 papers at NeurIPS? In the authors column of the database, each entry is a list, not a single string. Return as a list of authors.", "answer": ["Karthik Valmeekam", "Sarath Sreedharan", "Subbarao Kambhampati"]}
{"qid": "easy-0566", "question_type": "2", "question": "What were the top 2 IPCR categories with the highest number of accepted patents in 2006? Return them as a list of IPCR categories.", "answer": ["G06", "H01"]}
{"qid": "easy-0567", "question_type": "5", "question": "Who were the top 5 authors with the highest number of publications where the titles contain 'Large Language Models' amongst the first 2300 papers at NeurIPS? In the authors column of the database, each entry is a list, not a single string. Return as a list of authors.", "answer": ["Yuan Cao", "Karthik Valmeekam", "Sarath Sreedharan", "Subbarao Kambhampati", "Lintang Sutawika"]}
{"qid": "easy-0568", "question_type": "2", "question": "Which IPCR categories were among the top 2 with the highest number of accepted patents in 2015? Return the top categories with the highest approval rates as a list of IPCR categories.", "answer": ["H04", "H01"]}
{"qid": "easy-0569", "question_type": "2", "question": "What were the top 2 IPCR categories with the highest number of accepted patents in 2005? Return them as a list of IPCR categories.", "answer": ["G06", "H04"]}
{"qid": "easy-0570", "question_type": "5", "question": "Which 3 authors had the most publications where the titles contain 'Large Language Models' amongst the first 2800 papers at NeurIPS? In the authors column of the database, each entry is a list, not a single string. Return as a list of authors.", "answer": ["Subbarao Kambhampati", "Sarath Sreedharan", "Karthik Valmeekam"]}
{"qid": "easy-0571", "question_type": "5", "question": "Who were the top 4 authors with the highest number of publications where the titles contain 'Large Language Models' amongst the first 3200 papers at NeurIPS? In the authors column of the database, each entry is a list, not a single string. Return as a list of authors.", "answer": ["Karthik Valmeekam", "William Yang Wang", "Sarath Sreedharan", "Subbarao Kambhampati"]}
{"qid": "easy-0572", "question_type": "5", "question": "Who were the top 5 authors with the most publications where the titles contain 'Large Language Models' amongst the first 1200 papers at NeurIPS? In the authors column of the database, each entry is a list, not a single string. Return as a list of authors.", "answer": ["Yuan Cao", "Lintang Sutawika", "Subbarao Kambhampati", "Karthik Valmeekam", "Sarath Sreedharan"]}
{"qid": "easy-0573", "question_type": "5", "question": "Who were the top 2 authors with the most publications amongst the first 1900 papers at NeurIPS? In the authors column of the database, each entry is a list, not a single string. Return as a list of authors.", "answer": ["Bernhard Schölkopf", "Bo Li"]}
{"qid": "easy-0574", "question_type": "5", "question": "Which 5 authors had the most publications where the titles contain 'Large Language Models' amongst the first 2100 papers at NeurIPS? In the authors column of the database, each entry is a list, not a single string. Return as a list of authors.", "answer": ["Sarath Sreedharan", "Karthik Valmeekam", "Lintang Sutawika", "Yuan Cao", "Subbarao Kambhampati"]}
{"qid": "easy-0575", "question_type": "2", "question": "What were the top 3 CPC categories with the highest number of accepted patents in 2018? Return them as a list of CPC categories.", "answer": ["H04", "A61", "G06"]}
{"qid": "easy-0576", "question_type": "5", "question": "Who were the top 5 authors with the highest number of publications where the titles contain 'Large Language Models' amongst the first 1400 papers at NeurIPS? In the authors column of the database, each entry is a list, not a single string. Return as a list of authors.", "answer": ["Yuan Cao", "Sarath Sreedharan", "Subbarao Kambhampati", "Lintang Sutawika", "Karthik Valmeekam"]}
{"qid": "easy-0577", "question_type": "5", "question": "Who were the top 5 authors with the most publications where the titles contain 'Large Language Models' amongst the first 2500 papers at NeurIPS? In the authors column of the database, each entry is a list, not a single string. Return as a list of authors.", "answer": ["Subbarao Kambhampati", "Sarath Sreedharan", "Yuan Cao", "Karthik Valmeekam", "Lintang Sutawika"]}
{"qid": "easy-0578", "question_type": "5", "question": "Who were the top 4 authors with the most publications where the titles contain 'Large Language Models' amongst the first 3200 papers at NeurIPS? In the authors column of the database, each entry is a list, not a single string. Return as a list of authors.", "answer": ["Karthik Valmeekam", "William Yang Wang", "Sarath Sreedharan", "Subbarao Kambhampati"]}
{"qid": "easy-0579", "question_type": "5", "question": "Who were the top 4 authors with the highest number of publications where the titles contain 'Large Language Models' amongst the first 3400 papers at NeurIPS? In the authors column of the database, each entry is a list, not a single string. Return as a list of authors.", "answer": ["Sarath Sreedharan", "Karthik Valmeekam", "William Yang Wang", "Subbarao Kambhampati"]}
{"qid": "easy-0580", "question_type": "5", "question": "Who were the top 4 authors with the most publications where the titles contain 'Large Language Models' at NeurIPS? In the authors column of the database, each entry is a list, not a single string. Return as a list of authors.", "answer": ["Subbarao Kambhampati", "Karthik Valmeekam", "William Yang Wang", "Sarath Sreedharan"]}
{"qid": "easy-0581", "question_type": "5", "question": "Which 5 authors had the most publications where the titles contain 'Large Language Models' amongst the first 2100 papers at NeurIPS? In the authors column of the database, each entry is a list, not a single string. Return as a list of authors.", "answer": ["Sarath Sreedharan", "Karthik Valmeekam", "Lintang Sutawika", "Yuan Cao", "Subbarao Kambhampati"]}
{"qid": "easy-0582", "question_type": "2", "question": "What were the top 3 CPC categories with the highest number of accepted patents in 2011? Return them as a list of CPC categories.", "answer": ["H01", "G01", "H04"]}
{"qid": "easy-0583", "question_type": "5", "question": "Who were the top 3 authors with the highest number of publications where the titles contain 'Large Language Models' amongst the first 2700 papers at NeurIPS? In the authors column of the database, each entry is a list, not a single string. Return as a list of authors.", "answer": ["Subbarao Kambhampati", "Sarath Sreedharan", "Karthik Valmeekam"]}
{"qid": "easy-0584", "question_type": "2", "question": "What were the top 2 IPCR categories with the highest number of accepted patents in 2013? Return them as a list of IPCR categories.", "answer": ["H04", "G06"]}
{"qid": "easy-0585", "question_type": "5", "question": "Which 4 authors had the most publications where the titles contain 'Large Language Models' at NeurIPS? In the authors column of the database, each entry is a list, not a single string. Return as a list of authors.", "answer": ["Subbarao Kambhampati", "Karthik Valmeekam", "William Yang Wang", "Sarath Sreedharan"]}
{"qid": "easy-0586", "question_type": "5", "question": "Who were the top 4 authors with the highest number of publications where the titles contain 'Large Language Models' amongst the first 3300 papers at NeurIPS? In the authors column of the database, each entry is a list, not a single string. Return as a list of authors.", "answer": ["William Yang Wang", "Karthik Valmeekam", "Sarath Sreedharan", "Subbarao Kambhampati"]}
{"qid": "easy-0587", "question_type": "5", "question": "Which 3 authors had the most publications where the titles contain 'Large Language Models' amongst the first 2700 papers at NeurIPS? In the authors column of the database, each entry is a list, not a single string. Return as a list of authors.", "answer": ["Subbarao Kambhampati", "Sarath Sreedharan", "Karthik Valmeekam"]}
{"qid": "easy-0588", "question_type": "5", "question": "Who were the top 4 authors with the highest number of publications where the titles contain 'Large Language Models' amongst the first 3500 papers at NeurIPS? In the authors column of the database, each entry is a list, not a single string. Return as a list of authors.", "answer": ["Sarath Sreedharan", "William Yang Wang", "Karthik Valmeekam", "Subbarao Kambhampati"]}
{"qid": "easy-0589", "question_type": "5", "question": "Who were the top 5 authors with the highest number of publications where the titles contain 'Large Language Models' amongst the first 1600 papers at NeurIPS? In the authors column of the database, each entry is a list, not a single string. Return as a list of authors.", "answer": ["Karthik Valmeekam", "Sarath Sreedharan", "Subbarao Kambhampati", "Yuan Cao", "Lintang Sutawika"]}
{"qid": "easy-0590", "question_type": "5", "question": "Which 5 authors had the most publications where the titles contain 'Large Language Models' amongst the first 2300 papers at NeurIPS? In the authors column of the database, each entry is a list, not a single string. Return as a list of authors.", "answer": ["Yuan Cao", "Karthik Valmeekam", "Sarath Sreedharan", "Subbarao Kambhampati", "Lintang Sutawika"]}
{"qid": "easy-0591", "question_type": "5", "question": "Which 4 authors had the most publications where the titles contain 'Large Language Models' amongst the first 3500 papers at NeurIPS? In the authors column of the database, each entry is a list, not a single string. Return as a list of authors.", "answer": ["Sarath Sreedharan", "William Yang Wang", "Karthik Valmeekam", "Subbarao Kambhampati"]}
{"qid": "easy-0592", "question_type": "5", "question": "Who were the top 3 authors with the highest number of publications where the titles contain 'Large Language Models' amongst the first 2800 papers at NeurIPS? In the authors column of the database, each entry is a list, not a single string. Return as a list of authors.", "answer": ["Subbarao Kambhampati", "Sarath Sreedharan", "Karthik Valmeekam"]}
{"qid": "easy-0593", "question_type": "5", "question": "Which 3 authors had the most publications where the titles contain 'Large Language Models' amongst the first 2700 papers at NeurIPS? In the authors column of the database, each entry is a list, not a single string. Return as a list of authors.", "answer": ["Subbarao Kambhampati", "Sarath Sreedharan", "Karthik Valmeekam"]}
{"qid": "easy-0594", "question_type": "5", "question": "Who were the top 5 authors with the most publications where the titles contain 'Large Language Models' amongst the first 1100 papers at NeurIPS? In the authors column of the database, each entry is a list, not a single string. Return as a list of authors.", "answer": ["Yuan Cao", "Lintang Sutawika", "Karthik Valmeekam", "Sarath Sreedharan", "Subbarao Kambhampati"]}
{"qid": "easy-0595", "question_type": "5", "question": "Who were the top 3 authors with the highest number of publications amongst the first 2800 papers at NeurIPS? In the authors column of the database, each entry is a list, not a single string. Return as a list of authors.", "answer": ["Ludwig Schmidt", "Bo Li", "Bo Han"]}
{"qid": "easy-0596", "question_type": "5", "question": "Who were the top 5 authors with the most publications where the titles contain 'Large Language Models' amongst the first 2500 papers at NeurIPS? In the authors column of the database, each entry is a list, not a single string. Return as a list of authors.", "answer": ["Subbarao Kambhampati", "Sarath Sreedharan", "Yuan Cao", "Karthik Valmeekam", "Lintang Sutawika"]}
{"qid": "easy-0597", "question_type": "5", "question": "Who were the top 2 authors with the highest number of publications amongst the first 1500 papers at NeurIPS? In the authors column of the database, each entry is a list, not a single string. Return as a list of authors.", "answer": ["Bernhard Schölkopf", "Mihaela van der Schaar"]}
{"qid": "easy-0598", "question_type": "5", "question": "Who were the top 2 authors with the highest number of publications amongst the first 3500 papers at NeurIPS? In the authors column of the database, each entry is a list, not a single string. Return as a list of authors.", "answer": ["Bo Li", "Ludwig Schmidt"]}
{"qid": "easy-0599", "question_type": "5", "question": "Who were the top 3 authors with the highest number of publications where the titles contain 'Large Language Models' amongst the first 2600 papers at NeurIPS? In the authors column of the database, each entry is a list, not a single string. Return as a list of authors.", "answer": ["Karthik Valmeekam", "Sarath Sreedharan", "Subbarao Kambhampati"]}
{"qid": "easy-0600", "question_type": "5", "question": "Who were the top 2 authors with the most publications amongst the first 3500 papers at NeurIPS? In the authors column of the database, each entry is a list, not a single string. Return as a list of authors.", "answer": ["Bo Li", "Ludwig Schmidt"]}
